Hey Samantha
Hi Samantha good afternoon
Hey flirty hi
Come on in everybody
How are we doing today let's woke up
Got a great day yesterday. It was fun last night
Ended up getting some
vape
Hi freeside you already like thank you
Yeah, thanks for liking the stream guys
Hi mr. Tricks
Help
Help I need somebody. Hey, Jay dog. How are you?
How we doing guys?
Hi, hey spunky. Oh, yeah, I should I mean I should have gotten maybe flour last night flour weed, but I got vapes
Cuz there were three for 60 which is pretty say three grams of vapes for 60 last time I got
like a two gram bait for about 60. So another gram. So hey, Ilya. Hey, babe. Hi, babe. Hi, guys.
Nice day. Thank you, everybody.
Hi, guys. How was
How's your uh, how's your morning? How's your night?
I said pretty nice day outside
It's a rip of yours. Oh, it's three grams. There's a 40. Yeah, maybe I got a rip up
But it was delivered. It was delivered. They're actually pretty good quality. Yeah, the two grams for 60 that was
A little bit expensive, but
They're out. They're the all-in-one vapes, too. They're pretty good
Cool
Yeah, I think I've got $20 probably in delivery fees, but also I got like 40% off. Yeah, if anyone wants to reading today
Let me know hi
Some courage for today
30 diamonds a member, thank you members.
Samantha Avery, awesome.
Yeah, I mean, it would be a lot cheaper
if I could go to the dispensaries,
but hey, everything's delivered, so.
But it was here about an hour.
Oh, thank you so much. I love you, too.
Hey, babe.
Hi.
Come on, babe.
Morning, Tricks.
Okay, what do we got?
Let's see, spunky.
Ooh, okay.
All right, you know, these are like a little bit.
Okay.
Spunky you got the two of baskets, okay
Two baskets
That's that'll be the two of baskets would be
The cups right two of cups so two of cups would be like a love offer or something growing in love
You can see they're very they're very in love. No, you know, no, they're very love two cups
This book says
Says plant Saturja and Queens light it says the image a happy couple pose cheek-to-cheek
They both have a basket full of herbs and the woman's basket is Queens delight root and his is
Saturja Saturja both of these herbs are associated with keeping one's partner faithful and maintaining their interests in the relationship
It says the positive a harmonious partnership with the process the warmth romance equality sharing
reconciliation, best friends, joy, balance, mutual respect, contentment, serious
commitment, emphasizing similarities instead of differences, and truces.
Okay, and then we have one of these ancestor cards. This is this one is Dr.
Grant. There's Dr. Grant. Dr. Grant is up. Looks like he's out planting something
or burying something. They do a lot of root work. And who do?
So Dr. Grant, that would be number nine. So this is the Hermit card.
Usually there's a museum. Sometimes they're different in this deck, but okay. So yeah, Dr. Grant is the Hermit.
It says, but he, Jesus withdrew to desolate places and pray.
He withdrew to desolate places and pray. So that's in Luke. It says, Dr. Grant showed him solitude picking herbs and roots in the swamps of Louisiana.
Dr. Grant was a Protestant conjurer doctor from New Orleans. Unfortunately, the details of his death are unknown.
By the time Zora Neale Hurston interviewed Dr. Grant and others in the 30s, many conjurer doctors were using herbs and supplies from catalogs.
Dr. Grant, however, was a proud swamper who preferred to do things the old-fashioned way by gathering what he needed in the wild.
Dr. Grant might have heard a few critical but often forgotten lessons.
1. Believe in one's limitless power. 2. Petition spirits unequal to man.
3. Know more than one way to get a job done and 4. Acknowledge that no two people or jobs are alike,
because a remedy that works for one person may not work for another.
Dr. Grant was highly sought out for his abilities and some cases was paid more than $100
an exorbitant amount of money for the time.
So when Dr. Grant appears in a reading, maybe indicate the necessity for some time to recharge,
nature to reflect and listen. The car is not just about sitting in the park for a
few minutes looking at pretty flowers or squirrels, it's about considering the
essence of the tree, the flower is a squirrel. So if you receive Dr. Grant,
consider the following.
You understand the importance of alone time. Maybe we better to stay home tonight. Silence is golden focus on finding out the truth
Be in the world not of it pay more attention to your guru or spiritual counselor
If you really consider the advice you receive about the issue, it's okay to take a break
To reevaluate things meditate more and follow your inner voice
Yep
But finally
There's nine of baskets and so this is like a lot of things a lot of things you have already that make you happy
you want you're going for that last cup that last cup 10 of cups, but
The nine of baskets says the card shows an aerial view of nine baskets filled with a few items that represent what human beings most desire
So you've got a lot of what you both desire so it says
Most desired cash and jewels, financial security and wealth, books, knowledge, a gator head,
protection, rabbit's foot, good luck, old fashioned biscuits, nourishment and familiarity,
a bottle of wine and toxicants, sunflowers, warmth and good times and passport for travel.
It's not a basket, it says, dreams fulfilled, plenty,
art appreciation, wishes coming true,
sensuality, rewards, hitting the jackpot,
happiness, pampering, the finer things in life,
financial security, prosperity,
obtaining your heart's desire, gratitude, and making it.
I hope you like those cards.
But Bita took my whole audience now. I don't think Bita took my whole audience
I wouldn't say that. Bita's been on longer than I have and she's also started streaming today longer, you know, so
Has it feel feels fine take she took my whole audience, I don't think so
Audience is not something that we own, right?
the audience is a
group of people that
That cut me out when I come here, so
It's a or where were they want to go so don't skin off my tits I
Wish be to the best of which everyone the best I wish everyone success. I wish everyone
Finds their audience, but there are two billion people on YouTube
I'm not gonna sit and worry about what a group of a hundred people do
And that's special yes, it's very special
There's gonna be a transform monster so it's a whole lot everyone be nice
Yeah
I'm happy I'm happy I started out I
Started out with three people the jet in a
You know six months ago
Already that's four times the amount of people I would have
Let's see here we go
Yep
Yep, so if I need to rebuild my audience. Hey, Gotti. Yeah, everyone be nice
you know
all kinds of different people
The place where everyone can come be themselves
Okay, I have a no judgment no judgment zone
Chicks. Hi. Hi. Hi, babe. Oh, cool. Hi, babe. It's nowhere for you.
Yeah, so I got a nice, uh, nice vape, you know, uh, you know, take a little hit of the vape.
I can find it.
Um, here, uh-huh. Where is it?
I don't know. I'm having problems finding stuff today.
I did.
We can open another one up.
Come here.
One second guys, I need to eat some food.
Yeah.
Okay guys, here I come.
Okay, I've got my vape. I'm sitting on it. Hey guys. Oh
Come on guys, let's let's not just not be mean to people
Here's the vape
West Virginia
What do you what do you mean, West Virginia?
Who's who's news did a flirty diamond docks flirty diamond docks nudes nudes. It's a funny words nudes. I
Oh, she talks raising demon. Was he nude in the photo?
Are they still dating? It was the news yesterday. Well, I mean, I heard some of that, but
I think they're still, but are they still dating? I'm like, oh, raising demon really cares.
You cared? Well, oh well, there's worse things than having your tick-pick doxed by a tranny, probably.
I don't know, I've seen a lot of a...
I've seen a lot of, I've seen a lot of doxing from both sexes, you know, there's a notorious female doxers too, so I
don't think it's a
male or female thing, right?
I think it's probably the century for embarrassing embarrassing things, you know
Hi Trix, hi Trix
In the middle, oh the human centipede, oh gosh, how would this be?
I'm stuck in the middle with you and I don't know what I have to do.
I'm stuck in the middle with you.
Let me see tracks for them.
Tracks.
Let me see them.
Sweet Lenore's in here. You'd like Lenore. Yeah, I love my cats. We're getting
Yeah, you're beautiful. It's beautiful
I think it's a little spank
Yeah tricks and
Nor well, I haven't seen marbles in a few days marbles, you know, he was gone for six months then he comes back and
He checks in you know, he's like that
Like that wayward son, right
Comes comes stops by checks and sleeps for a few days and it's gone his way again, right?
That's a tune of tuna rig. Yeah, I just I just put out some cans
be it an egg dash milk for oh okay try that
I don't know cats like cats the cats like raw egg or cooked egg
I lost my marbles yeah I lost my marbles yeah I lost marbles but marbles marbles usually returns
you know I've I've had unfortunately
You know, I had a lot of wonderful cats disappear.
But this is a neighborhood where they have egg lovers, cat lovers.
I've seen some of my cats have, and I don't know, there's just a lot of cat lovers here
and they take good care of the cats, but cats go where they want to go, you know, especially
male cats.
They tend to wander.
And so, you know, Trix is my only male cat other than Marbles.
I didn't Rudy Rudy's a male cat, but Rudy you know Rudy's fixed but when they're not fixed some of the males weren't fixed
So they just wander
It happens like all around the same time too
The train right
It tricks told you egg egg now, okay. Well, I'm gonna go to the I'm gonna go to the
a butter blob. I'm gonna go to the supermarket. I think I'll pick up some treats and get some
laundry detergent. And
he's not sad. He's happy because he's chasing
All right, okay, Dougie Doug
Good to see ya
Sorry if I missed you when you came in
But we were reading about the cars like different cars in this devil's picture book
Today, let's read about one about the Empress.
Let's read the Empress today.
So this is the Empress card.
It says, nevertheless, it should be not omitted that some evil women converted back to Satan's
allegiance and seduced by the deceptions and illusions of demons believe or profess that
they ride out by night on beasts with Diana or Herodias, the pagan goddess, and an innumerable
number of women and cover great distances in the sounds of the night and on certain nights
are called into the service.
So it says, So reads the Canon Episcopy, a collection of injunctions against sorcery
900 AD by a certain Regino Abit of Prum. It is one of the significant documents which
bridged the gap between classical paganism and the practices of Leland's witches in the 19th
century. The mysterious figure known as the Empress in modern tarot packs represents this
pagan goddess. Both comparative religions and Jungian psychology refer to her broadly as the
earth mother, mother nature. She is the mother of Dionysus. So that's interesting because
It makes me think of the goddess Sibyl, and there's a goddess Sibyl, and she has a son
named Addis, and she's also called the earth mother, the rock mother, the mother of the
rock, and all that kind of stuff.
Yeah, it says what will latter-day?
Synchronic syncretic pain and paganism came under the direct fire of the Christian church around the 4th century the mother goddesses of various
Pantheons that already been linked to different speak aspects of one another
Thus in the South Gaia
Rea and Demeter were seen as Greek manifestations of Roman telus ops and Ceres or Sybil
The Asian mountain mother in the north their cults were mirrored in those of Nerthus frig and Freya
Essentially, the earth mother was seen as the patroness of all growth and fertility,
and the mistress of all motherhood.
All young defenseless things were under her protection.
Many legends were told of her.
Most of them revolve around her search for a loved one of some sort, the eternal shamanic
theme, which we examine in the preceding chapter.
Demeter searches for her abducted daughter Persephone, Ishtar for her lover Tammuz, Sibyl
for Addis, and the North Freya searches for Freya and Frey for Balder.
She is destined to wander the earth, either on foot or in her chariot drawn by mountain
cats.
In some various of the stories, the place of the lost lover is taken by an object.
For the North Scott is Sif, it was her golden tresses which were stolen.
Brissig Gaumann pilfered by the ever-present troublemaker, Loki.
Hey, Jamie's Cowboys. Hey, Arthur.
In the different branch of the same myth, Loki contrives the death of the goddess's beloved in this distance balder.
the beautiful and northern version of Dionysus Orocyrus.
Then we see that as well, being a goddess of life and joy,
she's also a sorrowing one.
In Matra Dolorosa, periodically mourning the death
of her beloved, always a lot of women who see their men
full go off to spill their blood and wars.
It was always the mother that's prayers were offered
for grace and healing, and the tradition passed
into the Christian church in the worship of Virgin Mary.
interesting stuff you're being shorted with that terror description well I mean
there's a lot more to it I just consideration do you want to hear this
entire thing that's great pretty long
By medieval times, the worship of the earth mother had degenerated to folklore, giving rise to agricultural beliefs in various old women and corn mothers.
A very few fragments of it remained in cult form, the goddess being secretly worshipped under such names as Habondia,
deriving from the Latinized name Abunda, Lady of Plenty, Diana, and other regional names such as Holda, Noctilico, Nocticula, and Bensozia.
The wild ride to warship mentioned in canon episcopy is not restricted to women, however,
men also participated. Neither were mounts, always horses. The canon expressly uses the word
animals. In Italy, the steed was often rumored to be the large cat sacred to Diana, in Spain,
the goat. While in Celtic countries, the hare was considered a favorite. In the public mind,
however, the shamanic riding pole came to be considered. The usual witch steed, following
who at her trial for witchcraft in 1324 was accused of possessing a staff in which she
merrily ambled through thick and thin, when and in what matter she listed after having
greased it with the ointment. The legend of Tanhauser portrays the goddess as specifically
anti-Christian, as did Aravya. As Venus, the Roman Aphrodite, she inhabits the inside of
a mountain where time moves at a slower pace than the outer world and where from mortal
Venus is seen as being direct conflict with the Christian Church and is in her great delight like Searsie's to lure innocents such as
Tanhauser into her enchanted realm to the damnation of their souls
Well with the advent of the Renaissance artists and scholars many of them drawn to a cult pursuits were among the first to take advantage of the
Las Pagan treasures that were once
being brought to light
It says Vincenzo Contari, an Italian scholar writing for sculptors at the end of the 16th century,
gives a description of the image of the goddess Ops, the Italian earth mother.
The sources he drew upon were ancient and he well could have...
been that they furnished the emperor's tarot trump with part of the symbolism.
She wore upon her head a circlet of towers, because the circumference of the earth is
like a circlet full of cities, castles, and villages.
The robe is woven with green plants and hemmed with leafy bows, thus signifying the trees,
plants, and herbs which cover the earth.
She bears a scepter in her hand.
Lions draw her chariot.
Here again we encounter the cat-drawn chariot theme of Diana, Freya, and Sybil.
Many early tarot of show the Empress in the costume of a Byzantine ruler such as Theodora,
indicating the influence of Eastern Orthodox Christianity, which the cards first came in contact with.
The tower-shaped crown preserves its shape throughout, however.
Behind the emperor's archetype lurk, all those mortal representatives of the goddess, great queens of antiquity such as Hephaestus, Samaramus, that Daito, Cleopatra, even Theodora herself, all of them regarding themselves as mothers to their respective empires.
When she appears within a card layout, she is said to presage a great fruitfulness and productivity, or a badly placed, a frittering way of energy, vacillation, or overindulgence.
Hers is a card of great beneficence.
but too much beneficence can lead to satiety and stagnation which is one of the interpretations
of the card when reversed. Oh, okay. I'm sorry. Sorry, Arthur. I scared some people away. Well,
that's about the Empress card. You know, it's about, you know, there's this goddess.
And women are the representatives of the scottish especially these rulers. Let's either this or birdo at betas. Oh, okay
Well, yeah, I'm sorry guys
Sorry if it's boring, you know
Okay, gaudi like gaudi appreciated it
the
Hicks, uh, I know I have some intellectual people here. Hey, Nancy. How good to see ya. Can I read about the moon card? Sure
You'd rather hear this, but we can hear it at the moon card, the moon card is a very
interesting card, you know, it's a lot about illusion, deception, cycles, and things being
revealed, secrets, let's see what, okay.
says hell has been conquered after defeating the devil whether identified as set, yalded by oath,
Saturn, or Hades. The initiate fool has by the grace of the goddess Isis Sophia or Persephone
has been given an underworld rebirth as Osiris, Dionysus, or Mithra.
The names of the gods differ from place to place. The mystery remains the same.
With the star, the reborn initiate begins his reassent, which takes him into the heavens themselves.
the same underworld gods that he has already encountered will be revealed to him in their radiant
celestial aspects. If you read the second formula of the book of thought, even if you are in the
tomb, you will resume the form you had on earth. You will even see the sun rising in the sky with
the following of gods and the moon in the form she takes to appear. Undoubtedly, the formula
and quoted earlier, and this is from the golden ass, this next quote, Lucius Apollaeus wrote the
golden ass, because I approached the limits of the dead, I trod upon the threshold of prosopina,
the Roman Persephone, and I was carried beyond the spheres of the elements, I approached the gods
of the underworld, and those from on high, and I worshiped them face to face.
The Moon, the second of the Greater Trumps, is the next heavenly phenomenon to be witnessed
by the Initiate after the Star.
Various Gnostic papyri still preserve rituals similar to the one referred to by the Book
of Thoth, whereby the Initiate could open the heavens after besting the powers of the
underworld.
Frequently identifying the Initiate with the New Moon, Jesus, these Gnostic scripts represent
It is boring. I hope it's not boring guys. I don't think it's boring
Essentially, there are three phases of the moon, and each was seen by the ancients as
one face of the great goddess of many names.
The thin pale white crescent of the new moon was the maiden, Chase Persephone, Artemis,
or Athena, the sprouting grain.
The full moon hanging red over the harvest fields was the lady, bride, and mother Demeter,
Isis Astarte, the time of reaping.
and jealous Juno envious Arish Kagao, eager to reclaim what she regarded as her own,
the sowing or burial of the grain. Most modern carot trumps simply show the moon disc as a
sensual figure, only when we study early packs like the Bemboject we find the goddess represented
in person. In this instance, it's a classical Diana holding a crescent moon in her hands.
Other designs feature a pair of astrologers measuring the length of the moon's ascension
with a pair of calipers or a man serenading his true love on a balcony beneath the moon.
Nowadays decks which feature a central lunar disk often with a face all that is left of the goddess in fact also depicted in Sirius flex
Or drops falling from it. Yeah, if you look at the moon moon, there's like these drops falling from it, right?
These are interpreted by some as drops of blood or by others more
Kabbalistically as Yod's Hebrew letter I or J the first letter of the tetragrammaton in all possibility
They simply represent dew drops
which were once thought to be drawn up and let fall through the influence of the moon.
Flanking the Moon, staring up at it, two baying dogs are usually shown, all that is left of Diana's pack of hounds, those hellhounds that guard the ways in and out of the underworld.
Two pillars or towers stand beyond the dogs, framing the picture. They are interpreted by more persecution-minded occultists as Egyptian pylons, representing the cobalistic pillars of severity and mercy.
They are more likely to represent the twin pillars of Hercules, which were once thought
to have stood on either side of the strait of Gibraltar, to the primitive mind the uncharted
waters beyond may well have seemed to conceal one of the ways down to the underworld, possibly
In the foreground of the Trump lies another pond, maybe it is a pool of forgetfulness,
or simply all that is left of the Mediterranean, or else it is just a dew pond from which dew
drops rise and fall. Out of it crawls what appears to be a crayfish. Originally it is
probably a crab, which according to astrology is a zodiacal sign governed by the moon.
This more than likely seen that the crab forms part of the magical nota, which provided
What's going on in chat? When I get distracted reading, there was some misbehaving. What's
going on here? Oh, you're welcome. You're welcome. Oh, hold on.
I'll give you reading. Do you want a reading for the clear diamond? I'm gonna be reading. I'm gonna be reading stuff
Sorry, I got kind of distracted
Well, what's wrong so I'm Jamie hold up guys. I'm sorry. I posted the link
Guys, hold on. I'm sorry. I got distracted reading. I just spoke pot and then I got really distracted reading
And so I'm sorry if I missed the link or if I'm going to ask, ask for a reading or I didn't say if I missed, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I was reading about the moon.
Hello. Good morning. How are you doing? Good. How are you? I'm good. What's that?
Hi. How's it going, my boy? Hey, psyche. I just wanted to get my reading on.
I didn't hear if you did anything yet. No, I haven't read you. Okay. Cool. Cool. Cool. Because
I had to sign into my fucking YouTube or whatever to go up here.
Okay. I got you a reading. Quick reading.
I want to know if...
What is my... I want to love reading.
You want to love reading? Okay. Yes.
Okay. Well, it says strength. So it looks like you have some kind of strength
Also, there's like kind of like a gentleness in the relationship like you know, where it's like it's not it's not a
It's abusive or anything. Let me see strength
Says while you're when you're faced with challenges and seem frightening and insurmountable strength reminds you to stay calm
Acting on a frustration won't help the situation now
Face any obstacles you encounter with a brave level-headed
Collectiveness if you do you may just discover the frightening beast you thought you were up against is no more ferocious than a dandelion
Okay pin the link. I know I need to pin the link where's my phone? Okay, and so you know
Yeah, you know, I think that's a good sign. There's no strength strength is always a good thing
Usually, it's like a you know, maybe you can tame the tame the demon, you know
This is my reading don't interrupt me
I'm trying to get my own reading yeah like this is the one of Spears which is like the ace of stores
And so this means there's there's like a lot of truth. There's like truth
You know, you know, you're honest in the relationship or there's just a lot. It's the truth. It's like it's like real
There's something like there's something that's genuine honest about it. And and
it's the ace of
Spears says the ace of Spears represents new ideas and clarity you've had a breakthrough and are feeling inspired to brainstorm plans for your next great adventure.
This is a great time for strategizing.
Okay.
Strategizing.
Oh, okay.
And there's just seven of swords, okay seven of swords this could be this but this could be some deception too
So it's like that. It's like truth and deception
It's like both there's seven of some seven of spears represents deception and trickery
Someone may be trying to confuse or hoodwink you pay close attention to your intuition now and trust your gut feelings
If the situation feels off to you now, it probably is
Okay
But and I'll give some advice for some advice
Okay, okay
Okay
It's a page of hedgehogs and so it's like I say I
Say it's a things are very new things are very new and so it says the page of hedgehogs is eager to help you and help you
Learn new skills
It is a bit ineffective at present opportunities all around you now
And so is the potential for working toward meaningful success and material stability
So it says the advice is explore new opportunities with common sense and your long-term goals in mind. Okay
So look maybe look at maybe look at things in the long term
The long long term what you really want in the long term and if it fits
So if you like that in the book Astro, so how are you guys doing? What's going on with you guys?
Also, I just come up and chill man awful
I haven't came and seen checked you out see how you doing and say you know see how you doing emotionally and spiritually, bro
So I thought I'll come see how you doing see if you're all right, you know, all right. Yeah good good good
I'm doing good psyche
Just wondering how you're doing
Yeah, I'm not getting a minute actually well a couple days I guess but you know I
Know yeah, so it's yeah
I mean I've been pretty much in my own show has anything been going on on YouTube
anything actually that you're changing your you're changing how you know you're running things now
Well, yeah a little bit, you know with like just a few mods a few mods now, but um
don't know it's like it just seems like you know I still have the link up for
people to come up it's just like you know we have different audiences we know
we go through you know sometimes you know audiences of some content creators
like you know Kate's really against me and like this talks terrible things
about me and stuff so and other people yeah that's how a lot of people are they
switch up very quickly you know but it's all about finding the right people to
watch you yeah
Know I have a great I have a great chat and there's I see so many like you know
There's a lot of members. We've been gifting a lot of members. Let's see someone that's coming on the panel one second
Hello
I mean you confuse me with that title and then there was no link I'm like oh shit am I drunk?
Uh, so you know Flurry Diamond and Raging Demon?
Oh shit, yo, I didn't even know that, yo, on everything I didn't even notice that they were there.
Alright, well, greetings to the both of you, lovers. How are you guys doing?
Lovers?
Yeah, I mean, they send dick pics to each other.
You don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
They jerk each other off. They eat jerk. Is that what you want psyche to do with you? I mean you want to join
Hold on what happened guys something happened
Was there a scandal huge huge huge not really I mean
Not really a big scandal. I'm not against gay people, you know, training people, lesbians
Honestly, they could do whatever they want as long as you know, they do them and don't include me
I'm good with it. Right. Don't bother me with that bullshit and I'm good
But
Your boy raging demon is notorious for wish and harm to like yesterday
He said, uh, I hope your fucking nephew gets great. Oh
Whoa, I never said that I never said that. Oh
No, okay. Well, okay. Why are you up here lying again, man? I swear I should beat the fuck out of you for that
So now you think you're some big you think you're somebody who's so relevant. Yeah, you know a football for that disrespect
You know what I'll we'll beat the living fuck out you for disrespecting me. There's no threat
Let's read it. No, it's not a threat. It's a promise. Oh, okay. Okay. Well anyways
Now he's been fucking around with me for more than six months. Yeah six I've had enough now of this guy
Yeah, you people are trying to cause me a mental break that now you people are trying to cause me a mental break
Then yeah, so for the if I ever
If I ever do go through shit like breaking down
I promise on all the blood in my veins
I will put your name and not everyone else else's name to go off the one by
Go off the one by motherfucking one
Make you all respect my name either respect my name or you're gonna regret knowing the name raging demon either one of them
I'll make sure I do it
Well don't blame us for what you're actually now don't blame us. Yeah, cuz you fake ass motherfuckers
It's all like use a lot of put like like perpetuating this. Oh, it's only internet. So it's not real
Yeah, so that means you're all your bunch of fakers then
You're all a bunch of fakers then now you're all a bunch of fakers
Isn't it was family members? That's my now, but you're all a bunch of fakers though if you keep perpetuating this
Oh, it's only internet. Nothing is real. No, you know, you've got a fake your faker then Amazon products from China
You're faker than Amazon products from China, you're faker than a $7 coin, you're faker
than a $7 coin, so don't give me that, don't give me this rubbish, you know, use a lot
of low life intelligent beings, man, use a lot of faker than $7 bill coin, like, use
a lot of space.
Okay, real great, okay.
Yeah, use that, make up fake stories, tell, say that certain, people have said certain things when they never even said it.
And then you're gonna act like, cause if, oh it's only internet, you're gonna tell people it's only internet, it's not real.
Well, that's shooting that guy that shot the guy. Yeah, remember?
He proved that it is real because he went off the internet found the guy shot him and shot the guy's family
Thank you. This guy is crazy. No, but I'm just saying you guys keep perpetuating that the internet is not real
But that guy proved it is real
So what are you trying to insinuate that you're gonna try to insinuate nothing
It's just I'm trying to like tell you people either start being real stop this fakery and be real
Otherwise somebody out there is actually gonna be real gangster and do this and this cycle will repeat
Now not me, but I'm just saying America is full of real people that will actually go do it
the
I'll give you a reading you interrupted my reading actually
No, I never spoke
Told you go fuck your uncle you wish you had this two-inch dick, bro
I told you to go fuck your uncle remember saying you the uncle fuckers song from South Park and then I left
what the fuck you shut your fucking face uncle fucker you're right i was licking cock licking
uncle fucker you don't eat or sleep on mother alone you fuck your uncle all day long
has that uh the stream just private she didn't delete it you do know that right
anyways yeah fucking weird anyways so i'm only gonna be here for one more minute
The issue is why don't you go home to your wife? Why don't you go fuck miss Piggy?
The issue is go home go home to your wife. Go fuck miss Piggy. What are you doing here wasting your time here?
Thank you so good go commit hop along hop along go on
You got miss Piggy waiting for you with her with her legs open
It's like, I'm nobody, I could kill less of your gay, lesbian, whatever.
No, well, go to your wife, go to Miss Piggy.
Go to Miss Piggy, I don't know why you're wasting your time up here.
I never supposed to go to your wife's name.
I'm not even going to let you get away with your name.
I'm going to do a burdo, you know what I mean?
Because I've been doing it ever since I was doing it in school.
I invented this shit, just to annoy my dad off.
So you really think I'm always going to start over anything?
Nah, I was born doing this.
All your motherfuckers out there really want to interrupt me, I don't think so, you're never going to interrupt me, because I could just interrupt everybody else.
I was just saying yeah, but I could just carry on going back to whatever I was doing
So maybe you're not letting anybody talk. Yeah, right now. It's just all about me, isn't it?
So you could just sit here you could just sit here all day and listen to my voice
Well
He was he was muted for two minutes. I'm joking psych. I'm joking. I was just messing with him
Smelly
What do you think about that?
Well, let me just talk to Florida Diamond for a second.
Florida Diamond, so what's going on right now?
What's going on?
Your dating region even now?
Why does it concern anybody what I do in my personal life?
Like, people made it such a big deal.
Who cares?
You put it on the internet.
They'll get bothered if the fucking people ask you a question. I'm not bothered by nothing Arthur
You're the one that wants my attention 24-7 every time you go panel
You want my attention every time you go and panel you want my attention Arthur literally for the last past week
You've been like diamond diamond. Can you please talk to me and I just been ignoring you the whole time
You're talking to me. So the question is are you and raging?
dating
That's none of your business.
All right, cool.
L.E.S. running New York.
Is L.E.S. running New York here?
That's all. What's up, man?
I hope the three of you guys,
the two of you guys can meet up.
You know?
If you guys were to meet up
before Barry meets up with Kate,
dude, that shit would
have me dying, bro.
Rip, Kate.
Rip.
What's up LES running New York, how are you? I'm doing good
Is that not raging I thought that was raging
Now I came in yesterday, but I just I didn't hear me. I just dropped down. Okay, so like raging
No, this is not region. This is how he us
Yes, okay
Do you know a flirty diamond and a raging demon and Arthur? No, I know I know
Stay turn
They turn it was on here yesterday. Okay, and I know I know
The other girl was on here yesterday
The one with the purple hair
Yeah, Marcy Marcy Margie. Yeah. Yeah, Marcy
Okay, so well we're asking him 40 diamond. What's going on with you and raging jeeman? Is there something going on?
Remember like you were on the phone with him when you were when Vita was here. I remember
Remember you're on the phone with him
Yeah, I do I smoke like I smoke and watch movies like why not?
That's cool
You're a faggot. I mean you're you're gay
Arthur, I didn't you smoke dick
Whoa. I didn't know you smoked Dick Arthur. How can you use that word when you yourself are training?
People are saying in the chat that you're a couple now. Yes, they are.
No, you would know any offer you would know you don't know it all of everything can it by the way
You see it's seen as you're such a know it. Oh, yeah, you fucking for it
Why don't you tell us how the universe works or mighty one or mighty faggot tell us?
Oh and he ran and he ran oh shit
By the way, good morning. Yes, man. Nice to meet you, brother. I mean you too, bro. Thank you, brother, man
So yeah, you see you haven't met for you haven't heard of Florida diamond LES
No
About stuff like
About that name, but I don't know
What'd you hear about the name? I heard it from a different panel. Okay. Yeah, you for the names come up
Okay, I get I get talked about multiple panels
Yeah, I've been to a lot of panels and I heard a lot of people with different names on different panels
Yeah, I just I mean I just heard that there are like maybe like was it was there some GM's or something exposed or what happened there?
When you told me no, I mean diamonds what happened? Oh, yes, I let me let me take the lead on this one. I got this one
What happened was there was a video that was put on disappearing messages, right?
There was a video sent to her of
Clip audio put together very very cleverly of
And it was edited to where it was made to look like I'm calling flirty a predator or something like that along them lines
And it was all just separate audios. It was just audio clips of me only but like it was edited of different
You know from me on different streams, and I'm going at somebody else may be calling him a pedophile
So they've took that word out from that stream
I think it was the one where I was on Samans and I was battling eight people on my own
They were coming at me. So I thought you know, I've got defensive
So I started calling them pedophiles and I called Sam and a pedophile supporter
Right just to get them off my back, but they kept coming at me
So I think they edited audio from that night. They took audio from that footage
put it together and made it sound and even then afterwards when Flirty fully woke she understood
she realized that you know it wasn't sounding natural the way I talk and whatever whatever
but before that like when she woke up all angry and just pissed off so that's what happened
and everybody wants me to go shout and scream at her but the truth is yeah why why should I
We really talked about shit. I really apologized
Yeah, and everyone's trying to make a big deal out of nothing, you know
But this is what it is like they haven't got content
So they're clutching at straws or anything grasping at anything they can find, you know
Hey psych
I mean, do you mind changing your profile photo?
I just like, I don't want to, I don't want to.
Anyway, I'm going to kick you in the back.
I'm kicking back because I'm going to roll the joint.
I'll be back in five minutes.
Why you don't leave, right, Jim?
Why you leaving, Papa?
You leaving?
You OK?
Yeah, I changed my photo.
That's it. That's it. That's
another photo. So, that's it.
Sam is again in his feet. Feast
about photos. I know but I
just like the one photo. Just
respect this. I did change it. I
don't have case photo anymore.
All right. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank
Let's say what's up? How are you good? I heard my name
Rager you good
Yeah, diamond
Hi chat what up chat what go ahead psych my fault. It's okay
You know diamond and Reggie demon. Oh, of course
Say say I know you
Say look at you. Oh, he got the drama back. Look. Oh
Drama back. He excited
We're just what I bought with a German lady with a chibi chibi with a cake with up
German lady with a Samantha he man. Oh
Come on site. Come your site. Don't show your hands up. What's right? Do not put your hands up
Don't put not you don't put your hand up. What up nobody site
I advise you do not put your hand up.
Hands up, don't shoot.
Oh, Sike, look at Sike.
Sike, I just look.
Yeah, thank you.
Switch.
Yo, Jesus Christ.
Yo, Sike.
I need another manicure.
Yo!
What up, nobody?
Yeah, you want to see salmon's dick? I exposed salmon's dick the other day see what?
You looking like you look
Try to force the thing on me look
I'm trying to do a second try to do my segment right now. I try to get a segment on
I'm here for the segment, what's up?
It was it was this is a jokie man. There's not there's it was on a pic. It was on a picture
No, it's not a salmon knows about that photo. I exposed his I exposed his photo a couple days ago
He knows all about that
First you see I got to confuse that first I posted a pink photo and I realized it wasn't Sam man's
So we had to fix that you got a YouTube too, right?
Who is this is the dude the dude on the bottom of me the one is in the train station
I put you in the train. You know, I got a you too because you've been in my choppy. Yeah
Nah, I got you recognize your voice and shit. Oh
I thought you was ease though. No, nah, you sound like ease. All right, I'll take that back
Did I thought you was ease? No
My for bro, it's all right. What a reality Nancy. How you doing?
Yeah, I got a channel my fall bro. No, just but I don't use ease. I was like, what the hell is LES?
Don't want to always on your panel and that's a salute on the chat. Yeah, okay. Okay
Man shit
I just heard your I just heard your voice. I'm like, I see you. That's the same dude. I go in his channel. I wanted
But did you know anything about what's going on salmon? I don't know what's going on between 40 diamond and raging deep not telling me
So diamond out at rager demon for loving the trance
Well, it's not a big deal. It's not a big deal like not a big deal. Yeah, I guess
Uh, Dimey did it to get beat up mad and here we go. No, I didn't that's a lie. That's a lie. I don't know
Regenerity said why I why I showed
That's I think that's script. I think you just want to get beat a jealous for hey, I don't give a fuck about me
They're like that. Okay. What about
Only reason why I showed what I showed cuz like raging said when I was asleep
Pretty much still asleep. Someone sent me a video that made it sound like raging was calling me a pred and a bunch of other shit and
Yeah, I showed a photo. I shouldn't have specifically shown
Okay, you out of him out no matter what you say you out of him out
Well, guess what? He's not mad at me. So what's your point? We already talked. We already talked. So what's your point?
Somebody out, okay for make believe message
Okay, and so so you
You he did he really call you a predator or no
Raging didn't call me that but I got I got in my feelings and I showed raging's the I showed his demon and
Well, I mean I shouldn't have done that and we already talked already about that and I apologized
How does it look
It's big. I should they caught it. I heard the nickname at the lobster tail
Lobster tail
Is it cutter cutter uncut
Video you know what they got they got the worst they got the worst of me for what like and I
Don't be smiling like look look he's smiling for the lobster town
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I
love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love
you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love
you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you. I love you.
Yeah, your dick pick got out. Look you motherfuckers turn everything sexual. Yeah, me
It's nothing sexual me and her hang out. We chill we got we laugh about these stupid this stupid ass nigga down here
We laugh about it. So why so you dig? Why so you dig?
Shut up for a minute. Shut up. I'm talking. Don't interrupt me fat boy. Okay. Okay gay boy. Shut up
Okay
Sam and that's what I'm saying
No one said nothing about that though is it? All right, so site. So right now. Why are you trying to change the subject?
I've seen psyching my name. Why see what was you doing? What can I say? I can a shower. You send your losses to the
time. Explain that to me.
Okay.
Come out to close it Sam.
You came out the closet already.
She's psyching the shower. Shut up, bruv.
You said I'm confused. I'm confused. I don't know what to do.
Should I read the DMs?
Shut up, bruv.
Just I'm confused you the first one brav how much money you worth? Oh my god
Yeah, you're concerned with my dick bro, what's that guy?
Why are you concerned with my dick group?
diamond not me
Why are you concerned with it?
So why are you why are you hiding it?
So would you embrace it
Fandom now I could turn I could turn to alright want me to be your friend just accept that that I'll be your friend
Except that you was in a sheets with diamond you send your dick pic you wanted to be with diamond. I'll be your fan
Support your gayness, so I've got no problem, bro. Fuck are you talking about crackhead?
You sent your dick to diamond. You say you was confused, but you love her you love him love diamond you said it
You said you love diamonds.
You people are sad.
Oh, Samman, you're trying to reach for content.
Keep reaching people.
No, you said you love diamonds.
What's the problem?
It's all good.
Crazy.
What's the problem of loving diamonds?
What's the problem?
Who said there is a problem what the fuck
That's what I'm so disemmitted you love him. That's it. What the fuck are you talking? Oh, you know what Simon?
I don't got it. So I'm gonna sell my lobster tail diamond. You did
My quick answer this then fat boy. What's it your concern?
There's nothing. It's not in my concern Papa. I just want you to be
Say if
Yeah, so it happened to me and I decided that I want to put a bullet through your skull and you
Whoa relax
No, no, no, no, you cuz you keep disrespecting me Sam and I'm just doing you
You continue disrespecting me
You and offer
Whoever in this universe keeps disrespecting me trust me. I'm putting a bullet for your fucking skull
What you talk to with it with the people that come out the closet, what you tell them?
Answer me this, papa. Answer me this.
Talk to the site. Rage in.
Sike knows how to deal with people like you, man.
Tell me this. Tell me this.
What? Tell me this.
Yes.
Answer me this. Answer me this then, Sam.
Can you answer my question?
Do you think I'm a joke?
No, you're not a joke.
Do you want me to actually find out where you are and I'll face you man to man and we can handle it like men?
I don't want you to send me a dick picture. Please don't send me a
Let me show you the level of respect to me is
Listen respect to me is sacred
What's the problem? I got no beef with you. You came
Felling me fuck you motherfucker raging fuck you raging
You're following me around saying fuck you raging, pussy raging, get that raging, raging this, that and the other, raging this, raging that.
Going on beaters and instead of telling her to shut the fuck up because I haven't even got near her, you went there instigating shit.
You know what now, enough is enough now, seriously, I'm gonna start fucking coming for you niggas now.
Because I'm not even wanting war, I'm fucking wanting blood.
I want blood
You thought we'll see who's real gangster
But diamond he's mad at me that you out of him diamond. What he's mad at me diamond diamond, okay
All right, magic one magic one magic one on your free time. All right magic one
Okay, magic one magic one. Why he's so mad at me that you out of him up. He mad at me
Get away. He's mad at me that you out of him up
Yeah, but why are you interfering? Why have you been on my dick ever since from day one? Why? Why?
Okay, I want I want interfere you want to be
Listen, I know exactly how to make sure you never interfere. I'm gonna find that way you and you're gonna face
No
I promise you I promise you you will because enough is enough
For the final time
Well, you're gonna make me sure you're gonna be begging for your life
You're crying so bad
Do that to you I'll make sure that happens I'm gonna have you begging for your life and you're crying so hard
It's not bubbles. I'm gonna make sure that happens now
Now you've disrespected me too much enough is enough now. I'm gonna make sure that happens now
Because you think I'm some pussy so I'm gonna prove to you I'll show you gangster now you want to test my gangster
I will show you it
And I'll make you remember me for life. I'll make you remember me forever motherfucker
Okay
Don't okay me because I will make sure you're happy
Diamond watch when I get all your pictures diamond
Yeah, cool cool. Yeah in me cool. All right, but remember what I said to you
My mother's grave
My own fucking news I don't I don't share your news. I mean you just threaten to
What?
I didn't say no, I didn't say no diamond
You know the one the one you cut the one you cut with your eyebrow up there
can i say something can i say something for months everybody's been fucking harassing me now that
i've decided you know what these people what you all believe that i'm some pussy across the pond
right and you're trying to test my gangster now i'm saying that i'm willing to die for my respect
i don't care if i die i don't care if i shot you sam and then the police turn up i'll die in a blood
I want to see my mother again so I'll die in a bloodbath with the police but as long as I take you out for disrespecting me
I'll go out. I'll go out in a bloodbath
Yes, papa
Okay, so what what is he doing in the photo?
Cool, uh, Rizzi demon. What are you doing in the dick pic?
Oh, he's showing his dick to Diamond.
That's a FaceTime call, I guess, to Diamond.
FaceTime, FaceTime.
Wow, that's crazy.
And it's like, you know, I don't know what's going on.
So
Pardon me for what I've said, but the disrespect I've suffered and I still was
Now just get into a point where I'm literally like, you know what I'm just gonna have to show these motherfuckers
How I'll get down because they're not taking me serious because I'm across the pond fine
I'll find out where they are. I will find out and I will make it happen now because they think I'm just some
Nobody they think I'm nobody from across the pond. So I'll show them on somebody now. I'll show approve it
And I'll because I've suffered too much.
Yeah, disrespect now to fucking show.
No, but why are you embarrassed?
I mean, you say your dick picture that 30.
Did you send nude photos of yourself to raging fight?
Don't worry.
I'm not going to shoot you.
You know, everybody has seen my news and social media.
Everybody has seen my news.
Oh, but did you say that you had a good question?
So you that's a good question. Why raise in a demon is so mad. Ask them that woman talk. Why are you mad?
Like, why are you mad? Why are you upset? Like, I mean, you know
On my dick ever since you've got like finger you find out I was around beat her and that you've always trying to find out
Who the fuck I am. What am I about this that the other? Why'd you keep in there, bro?
Why'd you keep hearing? Why'd you keep in the fear in my guy?
What interfered with you and beta? And also you what?
Everything everything you just
The things yeah, she used to tell me you doing this shit what she's to tell you what Rachel tell me
Go and ask her niggas since you know her so much in it. You know it so well. Don't you gone see if she tells you the truth about this one
Yo, let's think of it first is Vita and now you mad that diamond out at you out and now you mad at me
Nigga just saying you scared about what I just said because you actually
Yeah, but you
What's up? What's up?
What's up?
Oh god, this retard is up here now. Why are you even fucking coming up here? Go away
Coming up here. Go away. You just got a smile on your face as I join. I see you're so excited already
I don't even have to see you. You already have your like you're smiling. Hello?
Somebody's recording
Come on
I'm not gonna snitch anymore cuz if I do like he's gonna be like
That person is recording but I see it's being recorded
You know what you said pathetic bitch the whole night you spoke about me when you got off the panel
That's all you did the whole night. You're sad. You're sad
I'm here for my boy, Raging Demon, what's up, dude?
Eh, not audio. Somebody face their audio.
With our page with our party somebody
I think there's a love connection between flirty diamond and raging demon and there could be happiness a foot
All right, you only you can go fuck your mother's if that's
You're not
Has your dad
That's how he is page. That's how he is
Man fuck all you fakers
You thought just mad
You thought just mad that I called you out for fake order fake love that you thought
Yeah
Fuck yeah, that's why you thought perpetuating about the internet is a real cuz you're a bunch of fakers, but that guy
What about that guy?
He's the only one who has a huge influence on your ass.
I'm sure he's 30 diamonds.
You don't even get your day straight, you were trying to clean that
I don't need you to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me girl, I don't need to know what you are doing to me
You have to even come back on cuz you're
Not bad mouth
Thinking about me you sad bitch cuz you got an empty life your soulless you got nobody you're gonna have nobody until you're dead
Raging demon diamond talk to I think it was diamond to
So if you two are in love, what why the aggression? I don't get it now now you'll be out of your dead meow
BKG incorporated you be alone till you're gone now. Why the aggression? This should be something we celebrate, right?
No, man, you fake motherfuckers.
You're trying so hard.
He's mad at everybody.
But he's not mad at Daniel.
I don't even mind being fucked up.
But it's not because of me.
That's a coin.
It might be because somebody else is fucking retaining him.
Shut up.
Nobody cares about you.
You're gonna beat him now.
You're gonna beat him.
Shut up.
I mean, you know how to say T, but you don't know how to say B.
Like, it's B-top.
My name is B-top.
But you know how to say shut up.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Yeah. Yeah. Mm-hmm. She'll be up. Mm-hmm.
What do you matter everybody?
Drink more alcohol.
You're an alcoholic.
We need to celebrate this.
I don't understand why they're so angry.
Ray, do you like digs?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
This is another day on the fucking game.
We're just having a field day. It's fine.
You're talking about me and talking about Reginald live.
We, uh, Freddie Diamond brought hot dogs and, um,
Raging Demon brought fucking balls and sausage.
Like, we're having a party.
No buns.
It was no buns at that barbecue.
It was no bread and no buns at that barbecue.
I got some melon.
You put a little bit of cheese.
The same day I'll find you New York. Yeah, what you live by the Statue of Liberty, right?
Yeah, he lives right there
You know
Because of me that's what you asked what you came up bitch
Nobody cares about you either you fucking
Hey, be nice to Payne.
Go ahead, Payne.
Not acceptable, sir.
Well, man, just fucking talk shit to Payne.
You're going to get fucking booted.
You're going to get fucking out of here.
What are you doing in our place?
Bitch.
I would turn to your relationship.
We're going to have on your it's going to be a lot more humorous
than what you just fucking exclaimed.
We have a lot of pages coming on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Could you put a diamond in there?
Are you scared?
Don't talk about me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You're the only one I'll see, don't talk to me.
Uh huh, uh huh, uh huh.
Well, uh huh, yeah.
You're not trying to get away
Look at me on the panel, we've been thinking that you don't feel her attention.
Why would I be telling it like...
Uh-huh, yeah, yeah, yeah, of course you don't.
I'm not gonna stop love, they need to go and watch a movie together like Titanic.
They shouldn't be on the panel, we should not, like, we should not stop love.
Reggie and D-minus Lordy should not be on the panel, they should be making love.
Reggie and D-minus Lordy should not be making love.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I can't heat up your-
He's got so many clubs and so many like-
He's got all this business that I've had, like they give him a one-year like, uh-
They're like, just for children, up on the panel, he's the trend.
Instead of going on panel, you fucker
Why don't you fucking watch your fucking mouth and shut it fucker?
No, thank you, you're gonna get your shit flat, not by me by T.L.A.
I didn't call nobody any bad name. I didn't call him any M.S.S.
She's talking about M.S.S.
What did you call me then? What did you call me?
You got them issues.
What did you call me the other day? What did you call me the other day? You called me gay?
What did I call you?
A restart? A stupid crying man maybe? What would I call you?
Wow, wow, wow! Raging steamer? What would I call you?
Oh, I'm so sorry that I said that either your mother or father
What you call flirty diamond, what you call psyche what you call everybody else
Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh huh. Uh
This is the new power couple folks
Can I ask you something does your sister sound like this when she's when she tries to speak to you
My sister speaks more like, uh, she speaks with way more immaculately and more beautiful than you and I could ever combine together.
My sister and both of my sisters, actually you don't know much, I have two sisters.
They both are fucking educated, they own their own fucking life.
What do you have? What do you have?
Wait, let me see, let me see, does your sister approve of you fucking dick and taking out the asshole?
Oh, wait, your sister invited to the marriage with you in Florida, who's wearing a wedding gown, which one is wearing a makeup?
You know, can you ever see yourself happy for these two and grace this, this loving couple?
Yeah, I think they should get them.
Mary I mean, I'm gonna be like
Like our tea we can go to the wedding we can be the flower girls we can have blogger like you know be the flower girl
But guess what?
You've never talked to my sister in your life, like you wouldn't even fucking know what we don't want to know about, so you just like literally make things fun as well, like that you think are slow or repable.
Guess what? My sister has been holding a job, we're like way longer than you, she has her own fucking business, she has her own property on the beach, ocean view bitch, ocean view.
Where are you in the UK with fucking like rain falling on your fucking apple? Depression is a hell of a fucking drug, isn't it?
Yeah, why are you not letting me say this your sister wanted to spend time with you
And you started swearing at her
Yeah
He's talking about sisters
Okay, take your breather
Get your semen get your semen out talk all the shit you want. All right
All right, I didn't talk about your fucking family you piece of shit
You want to talk about my sister my sister is way more educated and level-headed than you will ever be you recharge
You fucking suck dick and you're a man
Well, so does psych to be fair. Yeah, but but at least he's honest about it
Well, I think
Reggie deepen is being honest about it. He's
Psyche doesn't like go around like saying he's gonna art people like in the ass like I mean
He just wants a little like he's been obsessed in like two years like pretty much innocent. He just like
I think we should we need to be happy for flirty diamond and raging demon. Let's just
Yeah, he's got a mouth on him. You're not wrong page. You're not wrong
I think he's coming to terms with all this, you know, he was outed and he didn't want to be at the time
But now there's that's a lot to take it
I can cook without mentioning like it does I can cook to the shit without like talking like about weird shit like they do
I will fucking trigger the stop
I'm happy for those two. I really am. I think Raging Demon needs to embrace this.
All right, one of the VIP you're gonna get the front row and you're gonna see this
Maybe keep her off the streets. You know, he's a man of wealth. He says you know, he can pay
For dresses and tuxedos, how's this gonna work? He's gonna wear a tuxedo
She's gonna wear a dress or if he gonna wear a dress and she's gonna wear a tuxedo. I'm really confused
Yeah, me in the middle somewhere
Maybe it's gonna be like Elisha like a Scottish dress. So flirty diamond. Are you in love? Can you answer that honestly?
I think you are I think the two of you are
You guys were protecting each other on panel. It was adorable
You're in love with the thought of beat us reaching demons in love with my name and flirty diamond is in love with
Jealous of flirty diamond. Come on. I'm jealous of flirty diamond because I was always like boring
And I was always wanted to be something. I'm not yeah, I want it to be a man. Yeah, I want a dick
Soon everybody's fucking seeing you
I'm gonna get pregnant by raising you man. You're used up. I
Don't want to be like you you're used up
Where's the sip on right now some alcohol to cope? Yeah, is that what you're drinking right now bitch?
Bitch, I'm paying attention to what you're doing. Is that what you're doing you're paying attention to you
I'm paying attention, right
Listen, I'm a little fucking cat and the bushes watching every one of your fucking moves from now on. Drink more, drink more and talk about me being a fucking drunk.
Shut the fuck up. I'm going to take a bongad and I'm going to ponder the fucking thought of you being a fucking retard walking on fucking blade at fucking age grad.
Alright? Imagine being born into this world to do what you do. Imagine.
You feel all your fucking nudes and everything to everybody.
Imagine and ponder and project.
You literally fucking have freak-offs backstage where everybody can see you nasty bitch
I someone went to your Twitter and saw that you had your asshole spread open flirty diamond
What's your point I got paid
No, I don't need to spread my fucking ass and balls to get paid. That's what you do. You risk getting fucking herpes. You risk getting STDs. You risk different dicks in your fucking mouth. You're fucking ass. You risk getting arrested. That's not what I do. I do fucking things legally, bitch.
Maybe that's what he's into. You can't knock that. Look at you. Look at you. You're literally abusing your body in this photo right here
Nasty ass bitch
You abuse your fucking body in this photo just be happy
What the fuck you abuse your fucking body in this photo. Don't sell photos
It's not really new
You abuse your fucking body and right here beta. Oh
Wait, are you like putting my body out there?
Thank you, are you letting like people like porn bomb you or like say, you know
You're not naked you're covered so bitch listen my body might be out there
But you still got a whole set of fucking hair above an update that you can't even get up
You remember
Remember how he freaks out that's what how much you get paid for five dollar
All right, let's raise you in deep and back up here. Oh, there he is. What's up, buddy?
I'm glad to see you happy sir. I really am it melts my black heart sir
I'm glad when I catch what you made, I'm glad when I catch all the mandim, watch, I'm glad when I catch you one by one, watch.
When I catch you one by one, you're gonna respect me then.
Fuck you Bea, shut your fucking mouth when I'm talking, shut your fucking mouth when I'm talking you horcun.
Oh
Go cook my dinner you bitch go cook my dinner you
Yeah, you got dentures as well, and why did you swear at your sister?
My teeth are f**king licked.
I had braces, my teeth, I did my f**king cleaning.
You swore at your own sister, you swore at your own sister in it.
Yeah, I'm not going to let you talk now, I'm just going to do a burdo.
Yeah, you f**king stupid b**ch.
All you do is get a courty-free cut, finish.
I'm finding ventures, you need circumcision.
Are you going to get circumcised?
Nobody wants to see that ugly turtleneck you have on your dick.
Yeah, why are you doing it for your circumcise?
Are you going to get circumcised?
and a new song by Tupac, circumcision, circumcision,
circumcision, fantastic, this is fantastic,
this is fantastic, circumcision, circumcision,
get a fucking edit, get a fucking edit.
When your father is a retard,
that's where you get it from, BR, you get it from your dad.
If your dad was smart, he would get you a fucking circumcised,
but you know what he didn't give a fuck about?
If your dad was smart, he'd be rich like me, fuck me.
Well, again
Stricken man, I'm so sorry I can't help
Yeah
You ain't got no life bitch shut up and go make my dinner bitch
Peter, do you still have feelings? Is that what this is?
No, I'm just here for fucking, like, fucking around.
Feelings?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Feelings?
Why have you been on my dick ever since you came across me? Are you in love with me?
Because you want men on your dick because you're a faggot.
Uh, who actually you irrelevant drunk bitch?
I'm happy for you
I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous. I'm jealous
Love watching the empty soulless retard loser shit, which I did you did the other day bitch, and I'm happy
Go live and say that shit on your channel
When are you?
How many viewers she gets
Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright. Alright
Thank you so much.
Oh really? You wanted to show it?
Yeah.
When you're like sending him, like, uh,
you're sending and exploiting this fucking man?
What'd I say?
I wish you the best of luck. I'm a whore.
Projection is a hell of a fucking shit, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, you wish me.
Alright, you watch the blade, you sell your whole body
for a hundred to multiple guys.
You're disgusting.
Yikes.
You sicko, you sicko, disgusting people shit.
and they're waiting for your father's bone.
Wait for your father's bone shot.
Only target for your father's bone.
Wait for your father's comb.
Your mother should have swallowed you.
Let him black, Archie.
It's like he needs to take control.
It's like he needs to take control, not me.
You're bitter about your disability.
You're fucking scared.
You're fucking disabled, retard, cunt.
You low life bitch.
Like on the 24th be the on the 24th. I haven't seen you. No messages since the 24th and you want to lie out your fucking ass
24th of what June of this month. You know what the date is? It was like
What was like three days ago? Don't message me bitch. I don't want to know
Like
I can cook you what I say what I say read my fucking reply to you
Read my fucking reply to you. I said, you know what?
Look at the smile
You can't tell me this isn't a happy fellow Wow
Wow, that's your truck
24th all you said was
Then I'm back up always wanted you happiness. I haven't seen nothing
Where you should your dick the flirty diamond look have a little smile on your face that on the 25th you message me on the 25th
You're a happy guy, you know, you need to embrace this relationship
Yesterday
Listen to me close. I'm gonna say they're so calm
Killing me cold
I promise you
No
It's all fun and games, but you're gonna take it out on me. I'm the problem here
Yeah, yeah, it's all fun and games
I
Watch rappers to your channel for you. Yeah, speaking like that. Go on. Go speak like that.
Watch what happens to your boho when you got ripped in the mask. I can lose several channels
and guess what? I can't get it like that. Like that.
You can't even get your dick up that hard. Disgusting disabled retard. Yeah, you're
disgusting. Do you know why? Yeah, your sister wanted to spend time with you and you swore at her.
They're in love. This is
Yeah, the video was out. I swear to God, I'll quit the internet. I will quit the fucking internet.
But they're going to ask everybody that's ever known me, everybody knows me.
I would never fucking treat my family like that.
I fight for my fucking family.
You're going to talk about that.
All right.
It shows how sad you are.
Be are that's disgusting.
It shows how disgusting and sick.
How sad your own sister wanted to spend time with you and you started swearing.
He's talking about my sister.
You want me or you want me to go?
I'll go.
What flirty diamond are you gonna meet a raise you divans parents at any time talk about my sister, right?
Yeah, you're an other like she can be cap or slow or he said like whatever he just keeps pushing you
Fuck your sister. You like that. Yeah, you like that. You like that too. You like the uncle fucker talk too. Thank you
Yeah, you got you literally got uncle fucks
Why would you say that
Like he loves to listen to it though
I don't like
Get her out of here talking about like uncle fucking which is really I guess like your TOS
All this fucking time I haven't said shit about your fucking family bitch. All right, my uncles are really good
Yeah, I'm racist, but you're the one that's talking about on clothes. I'm fucking raised
Yeah, cuz I'm Middle Eastern you assume that my uncle would fuck
I never talked about that you willingly spread your legs open for him
Adorable
You know the sharpest tool in the fucking shit, but you literally saying I'm fucking Middle Eastern and my uncle fucked me
And psyche is like sitting there, but if they stayed about the Jews
He would be really offended, right?
How does it feel that you know your family got bombed by Trump?
How does it feel?
No one gives a fuck.
It would be quite honest, man.
I don't even bomb people too.
How does it feel to go low and be a piece of shit?
So if my family got bombed, did that give you enjoyment?
If my family got bombed, does that make you fucking get iraq?
I didn't put a jump and then a bum.
What are you doing in the back?
Wagen, watch your mouth and put them back.
Go ahead, keep talking your shit, bitch.
You fucking nasty whore.
You got me. Watch your mouth.
Keep it clean.
I just feel like, you know, about your family got bombed by God.
But I see, Ken.
He's scared to kick her off.
He's scared he might get a fly.
Keep it clean.
Oh, fly.
Yeah, maybe he doesn't fucking kick her.
I'll flag him. I'll make that fucking point.
You keep talking about my fucking family, my fucking country, like, no.
Stikey, do you fucking shit. Kick that bitch.
You want the money? You want the 25? You want the 25?
That's what you want?
No, is it be his channels like is it be
I can slide them and I will.
If you don't remote them, I will slide you.
Is this your channel?
Well, figure it out.
B-tard.
All right.
Your monitor died.
B-tard.
Can you hear me?
When I saw your own panel
Yeah, yes, like is this beat his panel? Yeah, is this beat his channel? Yes, like
What diamond?
me
Answer me
Page calm down. I'm talking to my brother. All right. I'm not gonna be routine. I'm not gonna be rude to you calm the fuck down
I'm not being rude
Why are you?
Who you think you're talking to?
Who are you?
Who the fuck are you?
Who the fuck are you page?
I
Was talking to you
Your penis is that why you you have a thing for diamonds
Get
Your channel brother
That's all I'm asking maybe this is the control that he likes. Why are you trying to dictate what he does with his channel? I'm not I'm not
Dictating nothing to him. He's like a brother to me
Shots off internet emotions
Now shut up Sam and no one actually to talk shut your relevant arse up when I'm doing that page for what shut your mouth
Shut your mouth when I'm talking
What makes you so happy?
It's time to leave.
Rita, you're on your own.
You don't think it's funny?
I'm gonna love that.
Rita, you're on your own.
Right, psyche?
I hope you fucking choose people that night.
Get them out of here.
They don't talk to me or page like them.
You don't know anything.
You have no fucking dignity.
You're waiting for a cash-out, you're waiting for a little bit of money, while he's fucking sitting there, and they bring you food, and they're bringing your money out on the floor.
Okay, I don't need to talk to trash people, I'll talk to you like, as a human being.
We don't need people, like, not to defund us.
We're gonna make a mountain out of a molehill again, where have I seen this before?
Where have I heard this?
Oh, when I was with her, every fucking day, every fucking day I was putting up with this
beat of bullshit.
You lot don't know, you lot don't know nothing what I went through with her, and you lot are fucking judging me, right?
But thank you, but thank you for trying to talk calm me down. I appreciate that now. You've been crashing out
Who actually talks a man for me to get this out of a system, right?
Man from just out of this again. I want to take on
Why is there any of your motherfucking business?
I am me, and I'm not gay, but you fucking dickheads,
because you want to turn everything sexual.
You want to turn anyone that's been talking to each other, yeah?
Even if they're talking to each other,
you want to turn everything sexual,
and you used to take over fucking honey.
That's a little gay, too.
No, you know what, no, you, you's looking to be gay.
Let's be honest with about this.
What the fuck is any, you know what, RG?
You know what? You keep coming at me, yeah? I'm gonna find out where you live.
Watch. Oh, yeah. Get in line.
I'll find out where you live and then you can say it to my face.
Now say it to my face. I'll find out where you live.
I'll find out where you live. You can say everything to my face and I'll put it before you.
Yeah
Now you say
No, no, I will give you a grand as well. I'll put a grand in your hand for you to say
What what I do to you after you said it to my face watch what I do to you
Just let me leave it at that keep running your mouth though, but until that day
Keep running your mouth, but I will give you money for even having the balls to talk like
We'll give you money for even having the balls to talk to me like this over the internet
But you won't say it to my face though. I'm pretty sure I would to be quite
And then you see, all right, all right, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, sure, yeah, you're pretty sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, all right, all right, all right, cool, cool, cool, I'll take that on board, I'll take that on board there.
Why can't you just be happy? I'm pro 39 and reading.
Why can't you die?
You need to consummate this.
Do you want to die?
I guess, I mean, I don't know, alright, alright.
No
That's the answer I need thank you so much
Enjoy the rest the evening because I've got the answer I needed all right. What's the answer? What was the question? That's even better
What was the question raging?
You say I asked you do you want to die and you said yeah, I guess all right
Then thank you for your
Look at you two sitting next to each other. I'll keep playing
I'm gonna smoke my joint backstage and let yous lot talk shit cuz you're little puppets
On my throne and let the court just
Let my
Yeah, entertain me, Jester.
You're not going to entertain your gay, let's be honest here.
I'm going to sit on my throne and I'm going to watch you clowns entertain me.
You're going to sit on your throne?
Come on, you're a gay man, it's okay.
It's okay to be gay.
I'm nothing like your father was, sorry.
Stop calling me what your father was.
Don't disrespect me like that.
I look at the smile. That's the smile of a man sending his penis to a transvestite that was gay
Gay
You come from
How do you think you suspect in me when your fucking father's a gay?
All right, well the day my father's in flirty diamonds dm's then you then you can tell me that yeah your father's gay, isn't he?
I don't believe so no you don't need so are you sure about that you don't raise you whatever you need to do to get through this
I will help
Lineage of fagotry
Dude, this is your face after you said
You're a product of ancestry though, so who you talk about me and you say whatever you have to say to get this
Evidential in your behavior and pattern
You want to talk about behavior being gay?
Yeah, now I'm
Your behavior your behavior lets me know that you see you
From ancestry
My for me I cannot for the life of me understand who the fuck do you think you are to come and talk to me?
Think you're relevant
Relevant enough to even be in my company go back down in the chat go go off the panel
You're not even esteemed company to be around me. Please go down. Please go down into the chat. Please
You're not esteemed company, you're not rowy, you're not
You are just irrelevant
Nobody cares about you
induced voice either I honestly believe you and flirty diamond could have a very happy relationship
chords on offer heroin though i'm so sorry that's a little gay that's a little gay but that's okay
it's okay but your vocal chords offer the heroin on off the pookie pipe that's all
I mean that's so unfortunate my man, that's so unfortunate, you know, you're a cool guy but you know what, it's so unfortunate.
Get off the drugs man, stop chasing the foil my guy.
Stop chasing the foil. Okay. It's okay to be a fag. Yeah, so sorry the drugs your brain man
The milk the drugs melted your intelligence and you're
Realizing of having a semblance of intelligence to hold up
Your face look at the smile just the smile
Is all you resort to you lack the semblance of intelligence to even have a proper conversation
Look how happy you are in that picture, dude.
You're lashing out.
You cannot engage me on no level whatsoever.
Because you are so fragile.
You are so fragile, irrelevant.
Your soul is fragile.
Your mentality is fragile.
You're weak.
I'm sorry you got outed as a gay man.
I apologize that you got outed as a gay man.
You have no leg to stand in a game.
Please, the stench of your irrelevancy is making you sick.
It is absolutely disgusting.
And you know that, but you got you got beat up.
Please don't go in the shower.
Go in the shower and wash off that irrelevance.
You think about me in the shower, man.
I think I'm like, all the time I go to reading that.
Irrelevant happen.
We got 30 diamond for a minute.
Raging demon.
What do you feel like?
From the star and then my reading got interrupted from this shit.
Like I had none to do with that.
I came in after.
Honestly flirty you seem like you're happier to and if you guys can find happiness together
I don't see what the big deal is
I think it's crazy like all this happened for me just trying to get a fucking reading
It happened because you exposed raging demons a gay man. That's how it happened
You exposed this man as being gay
You can't say I started that.
I did not say he was gay once and never once came out of my mouth.
If we're bringing the two closer together, why not?
I never called him fucking gay at all.
You don't have to call him gay.
It's just a word.
You expose actions that were gay.
He's not gay. He's not gay.
Okay, he's not gay. Whatever you want to call it.
But the fact is you expose his DMs of you two being very sexual together
Because your souls
You people have absolutely nothing in your lives in no direction you know your lives are over for most of you and you can't
The irrelevance
That you're looking for
I
Reading and then all this fucking happens
Ranging demon is a gay man. That's why this happened. So let's be never
Because you expose him as a gay man
is these fatherhoods.
Some things don't need to be said.
I suppose these family is baggage.
And you're the one hyper-fixated on games.
Are you gay then?
Are you gay?
Are you hyper-fixated on games?
Oh, gee.
You're hyper-fixated on games.
Are you the one hyper-fixated on shit that you're not gay?
So why are you hyper-fixated on sex?
You exposed him as a gay man, Florida.
I didn't do that.
You were hyper-fixated on...
You did that.
You are hyperfixated on sexual messages
that you have on your pocket.
You don't like the label.
Maybe we could come up with a different name for it.
By your own definition, you're a faggot,
because you're hyperfixated on shit that you can't do.
Who are saying this is scripted is you're not even close.
No one wants to be outed as a gay man.
So I don't believe this is scripted.
I absolutely do not.
Look how hurt you are.
You are hyperfixated on shit that you can't do.
I didn't do that. I didn't do that on his dick. Look at you. You have a photo of him fucking. What touching himself.
You're hyper fixated on his. It was some show. How happy for being hyper fixated on it on that smile. It's a great smile. Look how happy
you're hyper fixated and you see it in his eyes. That's a man who's looking for happiness.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm about to drop the bombshell. What the fuck are you men doing looking at my dick anyway, men?
What the fuck are you men doing looking at my dick anyway?
I had a lot of people looked at and they all said it doesn't look normal.
But what are you doing? What the fuck are you doing looking at, RG?
You have a mangled penis, sir.
Wait, but what are you doing to even...
Yeah, well why would you look at it in the first place to even say that?
There's not a person in this
Busted busted. That's it game over
You're looking at my cock faggot
It doesn't look healthy. What was you doing looking at my dick though? It doesn't look healthy. What was you doing looking at my dick though?
What was you doing?
Everyone saw bloggers
Like it's weird to me that you're hyper fixated on it
You're lying
Oh
Everyone to see your dick, dude. Yeah, what was you doing looking at it though?
You can take flirty diamond for that. What was you doing looking at it?
Yeah, you're in love with my dick
Homo smile homo homo. Yeah, you have to edit the picture though. So you get the picture
Yeah, what you doing actually I didn't see that
What was you doing looking at my dick though dude everyone saw it
It was like, yeah, that's your that's your main way in it, but you can't explain what you was doing
Yeah, you're sorry it was like no thanks. Uh, yeah change the change change it to everybody else
What the fuck you are g was doing look at my dick mean about 300 other people explain it to me in three
two, one, ding, ding, ding, gone.
Sure, I'm going to explain it right now.
I looked at it because Flirty Diamond exposed you to everyone.
Yeah, you wanted to suck it.
You wanted to suck it, yeah, me.
You wanted to suck it.
You want to use the bracket next time I take it, homo.
Listen, I can sit here and you can abuse me. That's fine. What happened? Well, how did you download?
Yeah, you downloaded the picture to edit it to use it as an avatar homo's look at that face. It's hilarious
No, I
You downloaded my dick
Actually, I don't want to re-pick what you're doing.
Ah, gee, ah, gee, no way I told you.
That's besides support.
That's all you've been doing ever since you've been on my dick from day one and been on my dick ever.
You know, you literally are the only person who's been on my dick actively, RG.
Yeah, you downloaded my dick photo to edit it to use it as an avatar. Homo?
Oh
See
Yeah, you're a homo bro. You're a homo bro come out to close it now again, whatever it takes come out the closet
Yeah, come out the closet though. I'm at the closet. You downloaded my dick pic to edit into an avatar
Black card G is a homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo, homo.
Every time you come on the panel, that's what I'm going to sing to you.
I'm going to ask you a new introduction theme, that's how you project it.
Oh, no.
Black Archie is a homo.
I can sing mother fucker raising them and you can sit here and abuse me with your words all night if you
If you got a dick pic that he sent to a tranny it's like second hand homo at that, bro
Well, first of all, the picture I downloaded was the balloon pic that was actually on Kate's fucking stream.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Nice excuse. Well done. Great excuse. You pulled that you're awesome.
How are you trying to put the game shit on me when you were just outed?
Like, seriously, you're mad, you're mad, you're mad, you're mad.
It's amazing. Wow, that's amazing.
Now, I give you credit. I must applaud you for your ability to pull that at your arse in 20 seconds.
That's amazing. I'll applaud you. Again, all you have to do is go on disc. I applaud you.
No, I applaud you for that, though. That's amazing and pretty. I'm a good friend, Reggie,
David. I'm a good friend. No, you're a great liar. You're a great liar. I'm a good friend,
and I'm going to say you're a great liar. That was amazing.
That was just wonderful that intelligence to think that up in 20 seconds like that's wonderful
I have to watch myself
I'm pretty sure that they're not aware that that's considered revenge porn, but I mean it is what it is
So who's gonna press charges? Nobody. Exiled one. Listen to me. Everybody. Everybody is perpetuating
Oh, gee
Again what you can say you're saying whatever you need to to help you know, you're not letting exiled one speak so stop
Gentlemen, he said
I mean
Even now you're over talking the gentleman he just sat down I didn't even fucking
Talking you've been screaming for the last hour
Yeah, I ain't even gonna let you talk. I'll put a bird on you. I know you it's called our content
region David you
Dance for me
You think I dance for you? You dance for me?
It doesn't matter. There's no escaping it. You downloaded my dick pic. Yeah to change it into that avatar.
I downloaded a picture with a balloon on it first. Yeah, of course you did. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, of course. Of course. Of course. Of course. Of course. You downloaded it with the balloon. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what you did. Yeah, no, no, of course you did. Of course you did, RG. Well done.
Okay, can we stop being negative now?
What an amazing fucking ability, though. 20 seconds he pulled that excuse out of his asshole.
I believe it, probably 10 seconds.
Yeah, he stuck his fingers right up there and pulled it out.
Fingers up weird. Why does he got to get weird with you?
Yeah, so you did to pull that excuse. That's what you did to pull that excuse at your arse,
though, innit?
No, why are you talking about pulling things out of assets? You two are really having all the fuck was it?
What the fuck was you doing looking at my dick though? You still haven't explained to me
It's you keep saying everybody else or you keep saying everybody else sorry
But you everywhere you you're a man who is who's supposedly straight
but this is the only angle you have you went into discord no you went into discord to look scroll down to find my specific picture
So you
To download the pictures so you can use it to edit as an avatar and use it
What the fuck you're mad at, everyone else in the world except the one person who exposed you
RG, RG, yeah you can't explain to me though why a supposedly straight man is downloading my dick pic
What is a straight man doing downloading my dick pic though?
Because it's funny
Oh, it's funny to download. No, it's not funny. You got heart. You're harboring some fun. You're harboring
Well, what the fuck you doing?
It's hilarious, but what are you doing?
Thousand people and hold on you're straight. You're supposed to be
Downloading my dick pic
All you keep doing is to say no because everybody else saw it, but you're not explaining
Why you open discord to go download that picture?
So I can put it as my avatar
It's still on your phone, isn't it?
Was that my PC actually? Yeah, so it's been on your PC, isn't it the bloom picture is
Of course and the real picture as well. Now. How did you know?
Cuz flirty diamond expose you in front everyone be your bad everyone else in the world
But flirty diamond because you're a lover there and that's okay
Yeah, sure, of course, of course, of course, yeah, yeah, of course.
Aha, really, really, how is it?
It's a Tigger rocket science figure out.
Is it? Is it?
Is it but you still can't explain what the fuck you doing downloading my dick pic motherfucker
Standing him the dick pics directly, so he ain't no to
Faggot and you're covering up for him. That's what it is
Now there's no covering it up, there's no covering, there's no covering, oh yeah of course the white people are coming to defend, white people defending each other again to cover it all up, cover it all up, but yeah, you downloaded my dick pic, I don't care, you're projecting right now, you downloaded my dick pic onto your computer, you're sick, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko, you're a sicko
Nah, man, you downloaded my photo onto your computer.
Yes, then you can edit that.
It makes you feel better.
No, it makes you feel better, dude.
You're sick, bro.
You're sick.
Whatever makes you feel better.
Explain.
Explain why the fuck you downloaded my dick picture.
And knew what to say to me.
And the first thing, yeah, but the first thing you said to me
on my phone the other day, you said,
You know looking like a lobster tail. How did you know? How did you know to say that about my dick though?
Lobster's tail
I said it looks it doesn't
Mangle-looking what's up summer we're talking about
Okay, can we solve all the problems?
You don't like to talk to each other. She wants to do a talk and chat.
So Flick, you can send me to Revenge, poor bomb. You know more.
You just send your dick pics directly to Archie.
Problem solved.
I hope you did well, Summer. It's nice to see you.
You too, sweetie. I hope everything's going good for you.
Thank you so much. Everything is going well. I hope the same is all good.
I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted. I'm just being blasted
Well, she did you dirty in my opinion big time and then she drank she started tagging me and shit
And I don't have me or Miguel have nothing to do with any fucking thing. She's
Why would she bring you should have never shared anything that you you all had in private and that's just my opinion
So she out of it is a game in and it's not cool, but he's not mad at her which makes everybody
I'll go check him on cause it's got an emergency message. He's all
I bet you do
Some I love you all right, I'll come I'll come on your panel with you on your next live
All right, you got if you can't forget to say I love you too. I love you
Love you so much
I love you to RG
Say it back for diamond. I love you side. What's up, man? What's up, bitch? Oh, I gotta go summer, but I'm sorry
Yeah, I bet you do I bet you do that's what you do is run like a little fuck a bitch cuz you do that every time
We I'm here to fucking talking you wanted me to fall for it. So here we are you low lame-ass bitch
He's gonna stand around with his dick in his fucking hand diamond they want to go exchange dirty messages again, I think I
Told her every time I see her on the panel. I'm jumping up a talker shit fuck her
Like, besides us ragging on Rage of Demons just having fun with him, what she did to him was pretty fucked up.
Let's be honest.
100% what she did to him was fucked up.
100%.
Why is he mad and lashing out at everyone else is my question.
Like the man just gave her at 45 minutes because he can't deal with the fact that this person
Was so fucked up to him like what she did was really discussed
Well, probably cuz she's catching more bullshit than then it seems he seems like he's catching all the bullshit
And no one's really saying shit to her
If you want honesty, I mean put yourself in them fucking shoes you guys capitalized on
No one wants to get fucking tossed on the closet and that's what happened
She exposed him as a kind of a gay man.
I mean, you can deny it.
I don't consider him gay just because I don't consider him gay just because whatever their
message is.
Well, I don't even know what all that is.
Man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man,
man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man,
But listen, guys, when something like that happens,
we make fun of you, right?
That's what guys do, right?
If that happened to exile, the one
we'd be saying the same shit today.
She's a man, so why don't you want to get on her ass?
Are you would need some art? She's not street walking male prostitute. I mean, what could we really say to bother her?
You're right. Her life is as horrid as any life. I could ever imagine
Right, then she that's how she makes her money
And she's proud of being a street walking fucking weirdo man or whatever the fuck
So it's more fun when someone like raging demon who's gonna react to being called gay
Even though his actions were a hundred percent fucking gay
You know, but the fact of the matter is all that aside, what Flirty Diamond did to him
was fucking disgusting, and the fact that he's not mad at her is very fucking telling.
It's very telling.
Yeah, I don't know. I know she's a fucking idiot. He's a fucking idiot and I'm talking about
Yeah, you know what else would be telling what gender that motherfucker really is if he pressed porn
Revenge porn charges against that motherfucker
It will never happen because those two have a thing for each other because I guarantee that motherfucker's going to mail jail
But I think it was fucked up that he or she came into this community
Not telling people what gender they are and let other people fall into that trap, you know
No, it's not okay at all and that's that's my thoughts
You know what I've been talking to the woman I have a huge issue with that
You know because like I was saying earlier if it's had been done to a woman
So many people would be like oh my god, but you know what I mean?
No, it's not right and it's not okay
And she's gonna catch the right one one day and she's gonna fucking pay for her bullshit
now i don't think there's nothing right about it uh... the whole thing is just
not a lot
and in fact
i would be surprised if more of what happens
and he continued
how to shoot that motherfucker one of these days for trickery
he does all this for attention, he likes to spotlight on him
so the fact that he dropped those messages on RGDmon is not fucking surprising to anybody
No one is surprised by that. So the fact that he trusted her in the first place. So it's on him
And so if we're gonna razz him a little bit about it, he's got a man up and take it
He's got to me because of course we're gonna make oh, I'm not getting into that y'all that's y'all's men thing
I'm not getting in
For an hour, so I'm gonna drop but you guys have a good rest of your panel. Take care summer session in the kink shine
Well, yeah, I mean, I'm not I don't have you know, I don't have a dog in that fight
But I just died diamond pulled me in by tagging me in some shit with the whole Miguel situation
You know what I mean? Y'all know me. I try to that's I mean, I had sex that's going on for him and
He did that to range of demon, but I got an issue with her
She tagged so this is what happened Excel. I woke up yesterday, you know, I haven't really been around
I've been super fucking busy. So I woke up yesterday and she tagged me and something now me and diamond squash stars shit
months ago over the Miguel stuff, you know what I mean? So I was like, what's she talking about?
I thought she's just tagging me to come on panel or something. And then I seen she put the video of
me and Christine kissing again, back up, and she put Miguel's fucking text messages back up.
So I'm like, bitch, what the fuck are you doing? First of all, this, you all got all this shit going
on with her and, and Reagan and all that, whatever all that is. You know what I mean? Like, why are
you bringing Miguel in this shit? Why are you bringing me in this shit? Like, not to get nothing
to do with me. You're foul for doing the shit that you've done, but that's about as big as opinion
So so she's not still fucking around trying to like
Convince Miguel that she is a she when she's a he
Fucking she's got me confused like she's fucking confused
It's just you know that Miguel's like not you know, I mean he's got some special stuff going on right like why are you playing like that?
Like that's just when you start
Don't know. I just don't think it's okay like be who you want your trans great if you gay great if you're straight great
If you're bad awesome, I don't give a fuck
But when you start lying to people or you start exposing people's secret shit on people like that kind of shit
You know what I mean? That's foul as fuck dude and
Anybody that has any private conversations with him and I'm talking about diamond. Y'all are fucking silly
Don't do that shit because clearly she's told everybody time and time again. She's gonna show whatever
Don't say it
Yeah, it's pretty crazy
That's lame dude, it's it's it's
It's not a weird
Oh, no, I'm thankful. I put myself in a compromising situation with a male or female out there
Oh, yeah, I don't yeah, I don't even do this for a guy
Yeah, and I'm very happy with my husband and I don't even do discords because it's just shit gets crazy and discords like I
Just uh, if it ain't on panel and you ain't hear me say it
Bitch you want cuz I'm gonna use my voice and say whatever the fuck I gotta say
And I'm gonna stand on it
So it's you being a door scored you got a record the fucking discourse just to cover your ass
No, that's why I did the discords a couple years ago
I had one I was like here
I'll you know let's everybody have a place where we can all hang out and get to know each other
You know to me did that shit turned into a shit show? I was like nope. I'm good
I did messenger groups. I've done that before that turned into shit
So I'm like yeah, I don't do it like we know so that was supposed to
Be the fighting was supposed to be on panel
We supposed to be in discord get to know each other and have fun playing games and I don't know whatever
You know, I mean
Man that shit's toxic as fuck. I was like yeah done with this. I'm not doing this no more
So yeah, I don't do discourse like this
Shout out to everybody in y'all distortion. I
Do it oh
No, I'm just entertained by the drama
Something's mentally wrong with me, but that's okay. Yeah, I know I mean listen, I'm a petty bitch
I like I like a little drama, you know, I don't like though
I don't like and like I said if it was done to a woman everybody blues their
Well, my god, oh my god, oh my god, you can't do you know what?
Yeah being like a female to male like
Yeah, like, you know, if it would say that roles were reversed and say say I'm just gonna use me and Excel because I don't want to
Use anybody's names. You know what I mean? Say I say Excel did that shit to me and me and Excel had a bunch of private messages
And he shared all my shit everybody like oh my god because it's a woman
But when it's done to a man, it's you know, everybody's just like oh, whatever. That's just like cool
It wasn't cool when it was done to Miguel or anybody for that matter
You know what I mean? Like adult lot like on who you are
There's a lot of gender specific things depending on what community you're in now
That's why I like team solo Dolo go to all these communities and they fuck it off
I love when motherfuckers cry about all the fuck shit that happens over the internet
They're like you can't say that cuz you ain't doing going through it bitch
I've been through all that shit. You can't talk shit on the internet for 20 something years and not go through some shit
Yeah. Right. Oh, yeah. For sure. For sure. I'm gonna give you a fucking sub story. Well,
we had a nice girls panel over on Bita's me and Tracy and Paige and a bunch of us. Oh,
speaking of Bita. Hey, Bita. Nice. We had a good girls panel. We have fun. I'm staring
at you. I'm looking at you. Listen to me. What's up?
Lordy Diamond is Lordy Diamond. We already know her whole spiel, you know, or his but you gotta like look at the whole balance
Raging demon is not innocent by standard in any means. He said
the worst of the worst of the worst, to me and other people, to psyche, to everybody, I think.
Yeah, I'm not making an excuse for his other, his other behavior. I'm not, that's not, I'm not doing
that about any way, just like, you know, against women, we also got to do it like against men,
vice versa, right? So in this situation, um, Raging is really, really mad at everybody else
Right, right. So why do we have to get the lashing was everybody page?
Angel me well, I'm not an angel. I'm a fucking witch according to everybody, but it's okay
I got to be called like all kinds of fucking name, you know my I should be this my dad this and that but I
I can say I can laugh and he'll be like ha ha ha you're exposed
But I never go low as fucking saying like your dad your mom your sister
So, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's, let's
But it ain't just raging demon. It's Miguel and it's any other guy that diamond has I'm specifically talking about what diamonds do it, right?
I get I get all that
Miguel is a lot more intelligent
Miguel is a lot more intelligent when like somebody like their friends like look this is not right
You know what he did? He was like, okay. I got it
They spoke to him in Spanish and but this guy raging demon is a
whole different story. It's all for attention. They're doing like a duo to try to get people
fucking upset and triggered. It's like ridiculous. You're embarrassing yourself like ladies and ladies,
gentlemen and gentlemen. As Miguel, it's a whole different story. Miguel is definitely...
Right. Well, it's not though. It's not because I've watched it and it ain't... This isn't about
No, but be do you got to listen to me here? What I'm saying? I understand. Yeah. Well, no. No, I'm right. You know what's to me
I'm got everything but like like, yeah, he was saying the worst to me. He was talking. He was like
You just same thing like flirty
You have to let me talk. No
But you're making it about a person,
making it about a person, Bita.
You have to hear where I'm coming from.
Bita, you have to understand where I'm coming from.
Okay, you have to hear what I'm saying. This isn't about raging because it's
You're not listening and when you don't listen then you don't understand what I'm saying. It's not about Miguel
It's not about raging. It's not about any of that
It's a simple fact that you're gonna continue cuz she's done it even when psyche would sit there and hit on guys
I spoke up and said that I might do don't do that to people that aren't comfortable with doing that. I
Understand what you're saying. I do understand what you're saying 100%
but i'm just saying for me because this is where i get their behavior i get the backlash i got like
messages and like screen recordings from slurdy diamond yesterday or whatever she said it was a
24th okay we're like whatever um early in the morning i don't want to like know about your
personal conversation with raging demon and vice versa when that happened to raging demon he should
not everybody else. Okay, I agree with you on that. I agree. Miguel is intelligent enough to say
you look. Listen, I heard and that's it, right? And that's what he did. But this fucking match
child breaking demon is not just about Miguel or just rage and demon. It's not what I'm talking
about has that they's not just with the region. It's not just what Miguel. It's not it's just in
Miguel didn't do all of the fucking shit. He didn't like pull out as strong. He didn't fucking threaten people's lives
He's not 50 years old playing this fucking shit with like 30 diamond. Who's are in her like early 20s
Come on like think about it and like really big
I don't know why you think you're gonna come up here and lecture me about something that you're not here
That's what you feel. I'm not lecturing you at all. I'm trying to give you a little about background of what fucking I went through
Baby, we've all watched it play out. Everybody has been watching it. So I understand what's going on. Okay, and
I'm not making excuses for anybody's fucking behavior and why it is a little weird that he's not going after her for that
Some shit, but again, I'm talking about what I see constantly happening with diamond
Because she's the one that brought me into this
Know and the same way I see what's constantly happening to me with raging demon. He keeps bringing me into
Don't hear me telling you and I'm not trying to interrupt you when you're talking about that because you know best on that
To you, but I do I always say like I have a my like my mind is like ADHD
I'll lose track of mine. I gotta interrupt because I'll forget
We are good. That's me. None of this shit is ever gonna get us
If we weren't good, like you think I would be sitting here and just like communicating with you
I would be wild and out like flirty diamond calling you names making posts about you calling you bitch and this
I don't work that way. I can have a uh communication with somebody that I find like actually uh respectable
I will have that communication. That's why I don't do that
That's what we're doing. I have never called you a word and you haven't called me back. No, we yell at each other. It's okay
It's okay. We do that we're heated like we're passionate. Okay. Yeah, we're just talking we're just yeah
Issues it off. I'm having a conversation box. Yeah, I love you summer. I do a lot
You're amazing. I love you too, girly. And I understand where your things that you've been through,
you know what I mean? I mean, I wasn't around obviously when all that was going on, but I do
hear the pain in your voice. I do see where it's bothered you, you know what I mean? I'm saying
with you, I think our battles are different and we came on the same panel wanting to see
like things, but our battles are different and I didn't mean to come at you or like blame you,
I definitely
Yeah, I'm not
To the exploiter
Way excusing anything any Vietnam not that's why I said I want to make that very clear
That's not what I'm doing or anything like that, you know, I just
She I've brought I haven't spoke on any of this until I got brought into it because I'm the type of person where I try to
Not get in touch with every single thing. You know what I mean?
I'd be there I'm trying to be there for my friends and all that you know or whatever
But again, she tagged me in some shit. So that's why I'm waiting for a psyche to write his book
And when he writes his book and he starts from page one and he goes to the
End of the ending. We'll see the truth. So where it started and who brought it to the table every time
No, it wasn't me. I'm gonna keep playing that game over and over and over again. It's like a repetitive behavior
I know and um
This is like it might be exploitive like to me you summer Christine raging demon
All of these people but some of them, you know, you literally cannot like take any credit for raging demon
says horrible shit and he should be off the internet. He says the worst things about people
and their family members, not just me. Fuck me. I've already been like heard. I heard everything.
He's been saying it about everybody. Page? What the fuck did Page do?
Very very that's why you fucking like step on my tail when like you know
People that like can defend themselves, but they don't want to be a part of it
Like you're gonna fuck with me. I'll defend her. You don't have to psyche. I'll do it for you
Yeah, yeah, well, I don't think I floaties around very but thank you for the super chat
Yeah, she left he left
He left us as soon as I came on the panel.
She said, you just fell for my trap.
She thinks this shit's funny.
Well, it's not a strap. You're the one that's the fucking clown flirty, you know at the end of the day
We got fucking titties. We got a vagina and you know shout out to the men that have dicks and buzz and they own it
Whether they're gay or like bisexual you've been fucking like lurking around as you're a female
You're not a female act like a lady. Can you do that for once?
83 in the chat. He was just up here. Diamond was just up here. She left, and he left with it. I
gave him a panel. Raging is still in the chat and easy cameras, massive out ordinance penetrator.
Hey, God, Barry saying that she's in discord. He's in discord wanting to come up. Get your
ass up here. Get your ass up here. I only want to talk to you. Me in summer, like, I don't know.
Please
How's everyone doing in the chat you want to come up I think the link is pinned I was like I get mad
Psyche I was gonna go live and just go like blast and like go crazy
But you know me like I literally just you know, I don't like
You know, I already scheduled it, but I'm not I'm here
You're having good panel like we're gonna fucking let this fucking show right that's what we're gonna do
We're not gonna like diverge
yeah, okay, I
Might do it. I don't know. I'm doing pretty good. I just
thinking of
Eating something
When you know all the girls for on page I got me a big or on her panel
I got me a big old cob salad. It was so good
Summer got me craving for a fucking cop salad like, you know with like no, but you know, I'll do the
Poochies like yeah, I want to make a salad soon. What are you gonna eat tomatoes and bacon and chicken?
Yeah, extra chicken. Yes
Yeah, avocados are really really good for you. That's a super power food. I
Can not live without avocados
Yeah, they're really good anywhere you live at you probably get some good ones, too. I
Don't know. I mean I live like close to the border like I mean
I mean, I know they come from Mexico too, but doesn't California
Where you're at
Like all many ones, but like to say like the you know regular standard size. They're like
The same price right all the cuddles and mushrooms are good like they're like a cheapest shit
That could be great. I'm on feel the noise. I
Want to get destroyed. Yeah, I thought they did. Yeah dream
You have an avocado tree in your backyard. Oh, you are so lucky dream. I would love to have an avocado tree in my backyard
Mmm
You think cucumbers are super food, too, if you know how to use it
Thank you. I'm not talking to you. Actually, I saw a psychiatrist singing. I don't want to talk to you. You're an idiot
What do you want? Why do you know what that's me? I don't understand. I don't want to talk to you at all. Actually, I'll meet myself
Me and Janet. Me and Janet together. You're racist. You're racist and you're fucking an asshole
You're racist. Yes, you are. Yes. I was like black people. Yeah
You got good enough of miss like fearless as panel for like saying racial shit about black people
And then you came on my panel and I ask you why you like black people. I mean fucking said racial shit again
I don't like you. Yeah, because there was that one black person that was saying that right exactly
Yeah
That's true
That is not true. It was one black person coming up on fucking fearless and fucking saying that I knew was that who is the black person?
That's right
It was a lady
She's not like
Yes, okay, everybody I'm just gonna let them have a one-on-one for a few minutes, okay?
Summer summer summer left
Yeah, it's about drink time
Okay, well that I'll stay up here for one minute
Okay
One minute ago stream
You've been up since 5 a.m. Yesterday bitch guess what I'm 15
What's up Devin?
Look, I'm tired of people calling me a fucking predator regarding Miguel. I can show you. I never said. I never did. I untagged you.
Well, I appreciate that. I untagged you. I never told you that.
The he-man is spreading the narrative that I'm fucking that I tried using Miguel and I thought so and reason why I uploaded shit because I'm tired
People saying I tried using him when I never did I didn't even know he was yeah, but I'm at least watch that
Yeah, I mean people are gonna troll you because they're gonna troll you for whatever you know
I mean, but that has nothing to do with me
When I never did I never tried using him summer now once
Diamond we already solved all of that two months ago. Yeah, well people
But when I woke up yesterday in a tag for now, I thought you were having me come on the panel
I'm like, oh cool. I'm gonna go over to diamond's panel hang out and then I see all that shit. I
Never it was squash two months ago
Like this is the only reason why I got I'm tired of people saying I tried using him when I never tried using them
I just thought it was I just appreciated what he said to me and tried defending me against Michael
Like we need I get all that sweetie, but I did never I haven't followed you a predator and people me he man was calling me one
He man
That's it, but that's not me
and Christine was going around agreeing with he-man and that's the reason why I should say what I did.
Go after Christine! She is her own person!
I don't know her out and I would have added her if I knew it.
She'd be honest with you.
Fuck it, right, Chris?
to tell you like you know what I mean like she doesn't have a page so I don't know you know how
that works but again go talk to her when you see her on chat or a panel she's a big girl she
can handle her own I promise you like if Christine wants to say that she never said it so be it okay
there's no proof of the messenger so that she was saying what he meant okay okay there's no proof
then of the back and forth but at the same time I didn't fucking you know
Didn't try I I did not try using him once
That's number okay, but diamond sweetie. We already squashed that we came on panel even Christine
And then we all started hanging out. That's why and I could promise you yeah Christine was in chat and shit yesterday
And I'm not gonna put her business out, but she was super duper fucking busy
Okay with some serious shit
So it was just like when all this shit started going on me and Christine's like what the fuck because we had you on the panel
We you know the mean like we all been cool
And because somebody else says something to you you know what I mean like I can't control what the internet's gonna say to you
I mean don't be messy, and maybe people won't be messy back. I don't know, but it ain't got shit to do with me
Don't what she's saying is don't slip in the shit that you put down in the pile. I only want to talk to summer
I don't want to talk to nobody else
That's what she's saying
Well, I don't care what you gotta say, I don't want to talk to you.
Don't poop in the field if you don't want to slip.
Like me and you like that's why none of that shit made sense to me yesterday
That's why I woke up and I got pissed off because I'm like dude one
I've been mindfully trying to not be into some bullshit because I've got a lot of real life
You know me every scene. I'm busy. Well people that watch me, you know in the summertime
I'm super busy, so I don't have time to sit here and I can argue with you for what I know you don't
That's why I just said I don't know Christine's I don't even think Christine has an actual channel to be honest with you
Okay, then yeah, that's why I didn't I because I tried to talk Christine in the first place and just she wouldn't show up and
You know, I'm not gonna fucking and that's yeah, so I reacted on my emotions
But I will say this I will say this if Christine's like if she really did say predator
She'll own when she said something she'll tell you be like, yeah
I fucking said that because of this is it is you know what I mean?
So, you know, that's all you think I could say on that aspect
Cuz if she was a if she didn't own her shit me and her wouldn't be so fucking close
But she'll own her shit
So you won't ever have to like really worry if you if there's some shit going on
I know I'll be the first one to fucking say whatever I'm pissed off about and I'm gonna say it verbally
I'm not gonna write it to you and chat. I'm not gonna do any that
I know that and people are saying that I I purposely tried to take that I purposely lured off
Fucking Miguel just I can try to use him when I never did that
I never fucking lured anyone off the track.
Okay, can we just, can we have a,
and I'm not talking about even Miguel, right?
I just want to have an honest conversation, right?
Sometimes, maybe, just hypothetically,
if you weren't messing in some of the shit that you do,
people wouldn't think shit like that.
People only thought this because I fucking of the fucking but you're revealed private messages whether it be in Miguel's not the first person
You know, whatever like
I saw messages with raging night and I know you have no real opinion on it because you know I do not you don't
Yeah, I showed I showed but but you also show Miguel's messages
Well, but you also show Miguel messages these people are trusting you to whatever and they're not the ones doing anything wrong to you as far as I know
And then you go and show their shit
So then you wonder why people are like using Miguel and that's the reason why I showed the messages between Miguel and I
We barely had a little conversation and during that time
Wait, but then it got squashed and then yesterday the females is just, you know, he fucking messaged him back and he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's back and now he's
Right, and we had that conversation and all that and you explained it you explained why you showed it
It was like, okay, cool. We're all we're gonna drop it. You're like, hey, I'm gonna take everything down
Okay, cool. It's been explained. This is the internet, sweetie
People are gonna shit goes on forever and ever especially if you're doing some of the same shit
People are gonna bring it back up just to fuck with you
And if they know that's why I troll is a troll because if they know it works a nerve they gonna do that
Yeah, I know people told me yesterday regarding raging. They told me yesterday. So that I mean with that ambition was I you know
No, whatever. Yeah, it's vow. I know it's the vow vow
Yeah, it was y'all can fucking make fun of me for not being able to pronounce another word
I don't care. I know what I am. I worry about the word. I know what you're saying
Yeah, so yeah, but it just you know what I hear of course raging what you know end of day people did try fucking with my head
They got the best of me and you know, I did talk to raging privately. Obviously. We've talked already since then
And it's just I stand I fucking yeah, I I made it a fucking thing
I guess and it's probably not gonna go away for a long time because that thing that was kind of big
You know what I mean, and it's that kind of shit and the only thing diamond
I'm gonna say this and you've heard me say it because you've heard me when I'm bitchin
But I'm gonna say it to you now, and I'm saying this is truly is somebody that
Understands how this shit goes. I'm an ex-sex worker. You know that or at least I think you know that now
I know that girl you have to be careful because this shit is not a fucking joke and I don't want to see you getting hurt over some stupid shit
Seriously
You have to understand that and I was in the industry for a very very long long long time and
Know
I had so many threats in me just because I don't want to meet them. I know how dangerous shit is
Right. Well, it's even more
It's that's that's that's that's I get that but when you do when you do things
Even to escalate already a dangerous situation because being in the life is very dangerous even on its best day
Okay, and so when you and when you do stuff to enhance certain things
I just don't want to see you sit here and do this to the wrong motherfucker on this app
And then my fuckers draw up across country find out where you at because nobody's untouchable on this fucking app
That's all i'm saying to you and i'm really this is
Genuinely i'm being very genuine. I'm not making fun of you. I'm not trying to drag you. I'm not nothing
I'm really trying to give you some game. I don't want to see that happen to you
And it can
I'm aware of what can happen to me like I know you're being you know
I'm not trying to sound like you know, I'm just saying like I'm very aware on how bad it could have gone
And I mean, yeah, I know me showing but I show a raging he could have fucking flipped out on me completely
I know that I mean he did flip out on me privately. He flipped out on me, but we talked
We talked about it either way and you're and thank God for that, you know, but you're also gonna have to understand
This isn't gonna just go away
Well, because well, I mean, yeah, there are the people that want content, but I'll tell you right now
I've talked I've talked to far as I think it was foul as fuck and I'm not looking for content off of it
That's why I'm not having conversations about it. But yeah, I'm gonna say that that was foul dude. That was fucking really bad
And you gotta you do you I know you could do better. So don't let this fucking internet bring you down to some bullshit
Cuz you I don't get you want to build your brand baby, but that ain't the way you want to build it
You know, I know that that's the only reason why I go on this shit when people are talking hella fucking shit about me
Spreading actual bullshit about me. That's the reason why I get involved cuz other than that. I'm building my brand
Yeah, it's fucking my brand. It's fake. It's just a training chaser shit where you know, I'm I'm saying things just to attract fucking chasers
And I get that I understand that but when you cross that line you fucking mean it genuinely when I'm posting out captions
It's not because I mean what I'm saying
But you know, but it's just a brand but it's the internet
You know what I mean, and unfortunately it's not gonna go away and then not only that but like and like I said I get
You know I'm say I look I'm a petty bitch. I like to talk shit. We've all heard me gut motherfuckers on these panels
I get I'm not talking shit's cool, but just there's there's a certain line
Especially when you're already a part of a community to communities
You're part of the sex work community and you know, I'm saying the trans community which are both on high
Anything can happen on a good day
You know what I mean? I know you don't need to create shit that because i'm telling you they
Listen we can talk you know about shit. Why are you involved in this community?
I haven't even gone live. I mean, okay
I've gone live the first very beginning of this new drama
But other than I haven't really been involved in this fucking life and people are like on this community that much anymore and people are still fucking
You know going on my own personal fucking lies and trying to fucking mock me still. I've been
And unfortunately well what you did here recently
I mean if you're trying to separate it that was like, you know, I guess it was opposite day because that was not separating and
You know, I mean and in as long as you keep agitating the situation
It's like, you know, I mean cuz trolls are gonna be trolls you feed the trolls, baby
They go they go come for dinner. That's just what it is
And I just don't want to see you. I generally do not want to see you get hurt over some dumb shit
Yeah, we can go back and forth we could talk some shit whatever but at the end of the day diamond
I don't want to see you get fucking hurt and the shit that you're doing right now
I promise you will lead to you eventually getting hurt. Maybe not this time. Maybe not last time, but
Eventually
Like I've only went on here because I genuinely wanted the fucking reading from psyche
That's actually the reason why I came up here in the first place
I didn't come up here for drama even though yeah, I end up getting to big old argument as well
And I know what I have. I know what I said. I know what I said also
So it's not I mean, well
Even if you didn't say anything you did one major act that it don't matter if you don't say nothing else
It's not gonna go away. It's not gonna go away today. I know I should have shown this dick. I know that now you shouldn't have
Know and you know, that's what we talked privately about it. And now I get it people are fucking like oh my god
Either just either this is only advice
I can give you you either go balls the wall and fucking you know
Whatever and everything to go and it'll never die down or you just kind of you know
I'm saying just play your role and just let it pass by and yes
People are gonna talk shit about it because I mean dude you again. That's a huge fucking thing that you did
It's not okay, so it's not gonna just go away, but the more you keep feeding into it the longer. It's gonna keep on in the more intense
It'll get
I'm just you know, I'm just trying to you know give some knowledge. That's it. I'm not trying to tell you what to do
I'm not trying to lecture none of that shit, but you know
Cleanest mess up girl because this shit ain't worth it
None, I don't know what else to clean up. I already fucking raise you nine
Everybody we're still talking
That's what I get that that's fine
And that's great that you all could just whatever it is
But like the the clapping back and the all that I mean, you know some shit you got to take on the chin when you if I got
You know, there's times I've gotten up here. I remember there was a guy me and him used to be friends
He started we got into it one day mark me about my traffic
You know that shit whatever right and I got it his ass up and his mom was dying and all kinds of assets of foul
I shit
And you know what? I had to own that shit and every now and then somebody will come through and be like summer
Da-da-da-da-da, and you know what? I have to own it because I said that shit and I don't want to keep you know
Doing it so I had to fix my shit. I had to fix my behavior. I couldn't wait for everybody else to stop fucking with me
I had to check myself
So you don't have to check take one on the chin and keep it moving
Until and as long as you react it will continue and it's gonna continue for a little while and you know what and do right
And what I'm not do you do right, but I'm saying like it's kind of you know, that's just kind of was a territory
Yeah, I know I should I shouldn't be exposing messages
With such a public public part. I know that
So I know yeah, I cost I cost the ruckus and I know
That now that it's just
The most craziness that people have seen because I mean I get it
I'm the only active trans people trans person. I guess in this community. I get that
No, I there's there's I think there's a couple other people that are trans
I haven't anybody. I mean, I know many Manson comes up here here and there, but I mean I don't like I mean in this community
Itself. I haven't seen that many trans people come up here
If that I've only seen me well, if that's the case if that's the case
Don't you think in some sense? You know I'm saying you represent my whole community. Don't do shit
But you're the one that makes it about
You're the way but you're the one that you will purposely at times whether you're trolling or not
I don't know but you make it about that
So when you make it about that then whether you want to or not you gonna represent that and you're not doing a great job at that
There might be younger trans people watching you and it's like, you know what I mean and be like I could never come out
I don't want nobody
Somebody nineteen somebody eight and twenty years old nineteen can be you know what I mean like or whatever even somebody
You know what I mean? No kids should be watching me this shit. I don't know. No fucking kids should be on this fucking community
You just you gotta do it. You gotta do better as a person and plus, you know, I'm saying you identify as a woman like do better
You could do better this ain't it
So all right, well, I don't want to hold the panel up. Thank you for untagging me in the shit. So, you know, just take what I said
tonight
Please I like what I like what summer said. I mean have you ever had to hell to bail of hay?
Sitting across from each other and put a donkey in the middle. It don't know what it's gonna do. It's gonna start
Now that you said that I'm gonna try
Summer I think what you need to come clear with is that you need to tell her what you already told her and you came out superior
Yeah, it's not about superior. I just hope she looks at my son. No, it is about superiority
That's what we do here in these realms. Hey, look you ever had a pancake? It's flat on both sides. I mean, you know
Yeah
Well one side's just as good as the other
All right, yeah
As long as he's got syrup on it
Right so now we need to figure out what's going on with you and that girl because you already told her you were already
More up on top of her and you understand things and then that's what she needs to get together with
It's almost like she's younger than you would you say that?
Yes, she's definitely younger than me
Yeah, so she's she's she just doesn't know what the hell's going on. That's it
Well, she knows what's good. She knows what she's there on. I mean, you know, she's just she's the only one it can fix
What she's there on so I mean
Summer you sound like a smart intelligent woman that went through stuff. Did you
Been through things. Yes. Yeah
well
You got it together. You've got it together
We got to work really hard to get where I'm at. Yeah, we got to get the other girl some help is what we've got to do
You just start using our brain that'll help her out a little bit
Well, what number one we have to start with not using we have to start with therapy and all that kind of stuff
That's what we have to do
Yeah
Well, you know thing things are you know what when you get to a limit of use?
It alters things
If there's hormone therapy going on at this moment there might be certain therapy that needs to stop or slow down
Right, yes, exactly exactly
Yeah, and uh, unfortunately, I don't have the money to act I like birdo birdo's cool
His voice is funny as hell. I don't think he cares
I like birdo birdo home
No, listen, I think what she can do is very talented that motherfucker could just talk
Boy, I think it's talented. I fucks with her, but yeah, I think I don't know I don't know what she thinks, but I like her
We were having fun earlier. I was trying to keep up with her, but I can't
Try luck
Anyhoo, so what's up motherfuckers somebody come on chat and join us. Let's talk about
She says what's up, I like anybody that says what's up motherfuckers
Oh
How are you doing today Zigi?
Where are you from you sound like you're from the south
You don't have to say what city I'm in Kentucky. No, I'm oh
No, no, no, no, I'm up in the I'm from
Born and raised from the West Virginia area. No, I'm in the fucking Florida area
Wow, I can hear that I can hear the West Virginia. Yeah
A lot of people say it's like Maryland
You got a little twang little country twang
Little country twang
Yeah, what's up with you, man? What's going on?
Shit Excel, what are you doing today?
Shit trying to wrap shit up at the shop
It just started fucking raining. So I wrapped it up too late apparently
Yeah, we had like a 10-minute like poured out of the soft
It's been hot as fuck red like a hundred and something degrees again today
I didn't say I wasn't gonna enjoy it. Yeah, I fucking love the heat. Oh
Me yeah, me too. I much rather have summertime than wintertime
Yeah, that's what I always say please you can still come out in the summer time
Hopping a pool still be cool enough in the wintertime you've got to hide inside
Well, that's why I hate people like in the winter whenever I was up in fucking the north like they were like
Well, you can always throw more clothes on and then in the South they're like we can always take your clothes off like
Everybody makes up shit
Well, I think I'm gonna jump down for a little bit I'm gonna
Yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god, yeah, I'm a god
Yeah, it's been kind of slow. So it was nice to have a you know, just a little bit of a little bit of drama and controversy
But uh, yeah
You know it's interesting
How's the chat doing any thing going on the chat sorry I've been missing
I hope everyone had fun
Well, I'm gonna jump down for a minute. I'll be back. Okay, summer
Yeah, all right y'all might come up here and just like you some company
Love you
Okay, love you. Oh
I think you miss me
I'm hanging in there
I missed you guys too. I missed you guys. Thank you for being here.
We had a lot of memberships donated past couple days.
This is really cool.
And really appreciate that. I'm going to try to look for some emojis for the chat.
You know, I've heard I can probably find some on some website. We'll get some uploaded.
special emojis I'd like to do some custom ones but not that not that great at
that I don't think so it's 305 today at the at the subway the deal is it's
called hot honey pepperoni okay loser hey hey but nice to see ya thanks for
A lot of people stopped by today, hopefully they had fun.
You know, my channel's still around.
People that tell me, oh, your channel's dead.
Your channel's dead.
I can still bring in 100 people to enjoy the show at times.
So the channel's doing OK.
You know, I know there's some crazy language, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
What are we doing today guys? I was trying to look at like uh deals of their head. No, I'm on the grubhub plus
Everything just comes up too expensive. So I was thinking about getting
The subway they don't have coffee
It's okay
They don't really drink they drinks from there
Might just go do you guys want to go on an IRL you go IRL to the liquor store
Maybe we'll sub it subway the way back or something
Today I'm going to be wearing a jacket. Hey Marcy
Oh, let me see. I'm smoking cigarettes. Yeah, they, um, they stopped selling, um, the, uh, the swishers and so
I'm smoking on cigarettes now. Um
This restaurant looks great, but no drinks
I think they have a why not burgers. My grandma used to love why not burgers. I know they still had it.
Okay, well, no pretty decent prices. They're coffee. Coffee.
Okay, well that looks good. Why not looks pretty good.
Yeah, that's what happens, you know, pan, you know, that's why, you know, panel, panel guests can, uh, really
really, uh, bring a boost to your viewers, huh?
Remember, you're in here making fun of me when I had 10 people in here earlier.
No, I think, I don't think Jamie's meaning Miguel, I don't think she means Miguel.
Yeah, so it's, I mean, oh my gosh.
That is flattering in a camera angle. Okay, gotta go loser. Okay, see you later loser.
Let me see.
Let's go on a little bike ride.
There you go.
Let's see.
It's a little bit cold, so nice tricks.
It's a little bit cold, so I'm going to put this on.
It was a little bit chilly yesterday.
Yum, yum, yum.
I think I got everything.
Oh, sure.
Hey look
Wish it was for me
The guy is still...
Bye
Yeah, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let me just, let
Sorry.
Okay, here we go.
Sorry, guys.
like this, there, now I got it.
Okay, let's go.
Why liquor store?
Okay, success.
Next we get head off the subway.
Yeah, sounds good.
It's kind of like a regular one, right?
Light, light is fine, and strong is fine, but we'll see.
Both of them?
Sure.
Yeah, for you.
Hi.
Can I get the honey pepperoni meal today?
No, it's okay.
Yeah, it's fine.
Which one do you want to go for?
I'm going to have jalapeno, cheddar, but...
Okay
I've got a six inch.
Yeah, it's a rock star punch.
I was going to get a coffee, but I can't really carry it on my.
My bike.
My bike's like that.
Your number?
I hit you back.
You're pretty good.
I know, I know.
I drink some home now.
I mean, I got some alcohol beverages.
And you say malapeno bread, right?
Yeah, thank you.
How are you?
Great.
I have this kind of pizza.
The pepper jack.
And this one?
Can I get chipotle sauce?
Okay, I saw pepper oil vinegar.
Yep, it's good.
You go please.
I want to get the drink.
Do you have an important thing for us to fix things?
Or do you have something to go?
Nine, happy please.
You have a...
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Can you cut?
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay, success guys.
it's going to right down my street to throw them back in
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
So, I'm going to start off by saying thank you to all of you for being here today.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
by bagel, i'm about to damage, oh, cigarettes, let's go guys, home, home, dance
Hey guys, we're there all right, but a nice three and a half hour stream
Okay guys, we're back I'm back in business
Lou
I'm back guys. Oh 22 people everyone left. It's okay. Hey, there's a very attractive man sitting here bicycle seaballs inside. Oh my gosh
Yeah, it turned out
It's pretty decent
Really good
Hmm
Good eat harbour
Spicy oh
Spicy meatball
How are we guys doing tonight?
Wow
What's going on beat us
Any exciting
You guys are being here. Hi Nicole
Every thursday. Hey Ziggy. Hey the one that jeeps everybody. I'm sorry. I'm back. I'm back back
Hey, it's buggy they went to the liquor store
Ah
Round a little bit
You got a subway
Oh God
What way way less expensive than ordering out
I'm not Jewish, but I've always had my best friends have always been Jewish.
I love my, I've been at my sister's half Jewish.
Where are you?
I'm sorry, it means flaming room. Oh yeah, flaming room.
Well, we absolutely have no lives because we're sitting here watching me sit away.
Okay, well, I'm hungry, you know, also, okay. Give me a minute. It's okay.
but i have said iqabala
maybe it is me
i know a lot of people
a lot of people do lurk but
Had a real
I'm pretty dramatic dramatic a panel
Almost a hundred people in chat. Wow. I know there are over a hundred people. I think we got to 110 at one point
It's pretty cool. You know a little bit since I got those numbers
You know, but the controversy does sell, you know, but
There's something to be said for
Something to be said for
Quality, you know, a lot of people will just come watch the shit show and leave you don't really
I like when people participate
Yeah, growing people love drama they do mean it's like
Everybody you know when you're in school, there's a fight everyone wants to see the fight right now and everyone's always interested in like oh
who's mad at who, and who's cheating on who, and here's the comment here. Thank you. Thank you,
I got great people here. You know, I'm also up ups and downs, you know, there'll be people on
panel, there'll be people, you know, coming from other places and stuff.
Thank you beauties me
Yeah, I try to try to spread a cool energy
Yeah, well I just know some awesome people very blessed
If you'd like a reading today
Got reading for you. I'll do more more collective readings
but
You know what's up. I'm in the panel. Come on up. Oh
You little dickens!
Cat keeps spilling my coffee.
Stop.
Okay, fine.
Great diesel. Hmm. I'm cat. Let's knock it over everything. I
Know what cats look cats do
Okay, oh
No, please don't say jelly guys mr. Big Pies traumatized me. I don't like that word anymore. It's it's like a
It triggers me
I miss the big pipes ruin ruin the word jelly for me. I mean, it's like it's like it was kind of a fun
Not like my favorite word before but it's lost all it's fun
Yeah, the cats keep knocking over the copies and stuff
You're unalive by crazed bad man forensics with struggles getting the DNA from
Some mean Celtic, I know I don't know I think it's because I've been digging in this back over I need to take a bath
No, you knock that over see you look at it
Okay
Okay, I'll read some I'll read I'll read random page from the Illuminati book
Illuminati trilogy, okay
Okay, let's just open a random page
It says, okay
This is from
This is called the Lumodotus trilogy and so this is called the fourth trip or he said says Jesus Christ on a bicycle
Then mr. Order he runs at a very good pace, but old mother chaos is winning the race
Lord Omar Kayam Ravenhurst KSC the book of advice the honest book of truth
Among those who knew the true faith of Muhammad was contained in the Ishmaelian
teachings most were sent out in the world to seek positions of the governments of the Near East and Europe.
Since it pleased Allah to decree this task for them, they obeyed willingly. Many served their whole lives.
Some, however, after five or ten or twenty years of such fealty to a given Shah or Khalif or king,
would receive through surreptitious channels a parchment bearing the symbol.
That night, the servant would strike and disappear like smoke, and the master would be found in the morning throat cut with the emblematic flame dagger of the Ishmaelians lying beside him.
Others were chosen to serve in a different manner, maintaining the palace of Hassan-i-Saba himself at Alamut.
These were especially fortunate for it was their privilege to visit.
More often than others, the gardens of delight in which Lord Hassan himself would through the command of magical chemicals transfer them into heaven while they still lived in the body.
One day in the year 470, known as the uncircumcised Christian dogs as 1092 AD, another proof of the Lord Hassan's powers was given to them and they were all summoned to the throne room and there sat Lord Hassan and all his glory while before him on the floor lay a plate bearing the head of the disciple, Ibn Azif.
This deluded one, the Lord has on declared, has disobeyed the command, the one crime that cannot be forgiven in our sacred order.
I show you his head to remind you the fate of traitors to this world.
More, I will instruct you on the fate of such dogs in the next world.
So saying, the good and wise Lord Hasan rose from his throne, walking with his characteristic
lurching gate, and approached to the head.
I command thee, he said, Speak.
The mouth opened, and the head emitted a scream, such that all the faithful covered their ears
and turned their eyes away, many of them muttering prayers.
Speak, dog, the wise Lord Hasan repeated.
Your wine is no interest to us, speak.
The flames the head cried, the terrible flames, Allah the flames it babbled on as a soul will in
extreme agony. Forgiveness it begged, forgiveness, O mighty Lord. There is no forgiveness for traitors
of the all wise Hasan. Return to hell, and the head immediately silenced, all bowed down and
prayed to Hasan and Allah alike. Many, all the miracles they had seen, this was certainly the most
greatest and most terrible.
Then Lord his son this made everyone saying forget not this lesson
Let it say in your hearts longer than the names of your fathers
We want to recruit you Haggard said the nine hundred years later because you're so gullible that is gullible in the right way
Jesus Christ went by on a bicycle. That was my first warning that I shouldn't have taken
acid before coming down to Balboa in Michigan to see the action. But it really seemed right
on another level. Acid was the only way to relate to that whole Kafka on a bummer example
of quote, democratic process in action, unquote. I found Hag Bird, in Grant Park, cool as usual
with a bucket of water and a pile of handkerchiefs. Pile of handkerchiefs for the tear gas victims.
He was near General Logan's statue, watching the more violent confrontations across the
street of the Hilton, sucking one of his Italian cigars and looking like Ahab, finally finding
the whale.
Hagbird, in fact, was remembering Professor Tochu's at Harvard.
Damn it, Celine.
You can't major in naval engineering and law both.
You're not Leonardo da Vinci, after all.
But I am, he had replied, poker face.
I recall all my past incarnations in detail, and Leonardo was one of them.
There you go.
How was that?
Chacko and Wild
What are you doing chat I
Don't know what this conversation that seemed to have anything to do with me. What are you guys talking about?
I finished my meal first, I'm eating, I'm drinking, I'm eating, I'm eating slowly.
I tried to figure out the crowns.
Okay, what is this?
Is this the Game of Thrones or something?
Fill me in.
Okay guys, well, I have no idea. I still have no idea what you're talking about, but I hope you have fun. I don't know
I'm finishing my meal some more miss Vicki's jalapeno chips
I'm doing good today. I had a little nappy. Oh, it wasn't much of a nap
I was just I had my eyes. I can't really leave my panel very long
Have a one on the private chat
Okay
It's not it's already cold. It's a cold sandwich
To eat it before it gets room temperature I mean before it gets warm
Yeah, but this book is great
There's just all this
Gold in this book
Yeah
That's everybody really into the Illuminati or eat. I'm I know I'm eating. I'm eating slowly. I'll eat throughout the night
Yeah, I have a lot of books on Illuminati.
You admit amazing bubble bath? I had amazing baths yesterday. It was called an uncrossing bath.
And it was a spiritual bath. And it took away a lot of negative energy.
And that's like, that's one of the secrets of the world is that when you, if you can change yourself and you really do, if you really do change, you can change yourself, it will change the world around you and, you know, if you do it for the worst, it'll, like, it'll, you'll project all these things into what people say of, like, yourself.
And, uh, hi Traveling Gypsy, how are you? Hi. Hey Trix, come on, come down.
Hi, Mr. Tricks.
Hi, Traveling Dipsy.
Yeah, you change the world by changing yourself, right?
So that's why things like prayer.
And oh, thank you.
So thank you for stopping by.
Great to see you.
She's just a great friend of the show.
She's a great mod.
Yeah.
And because it gives us so much of the world is what you know, we we're attracting things
We're like this law of attraction. We attract these things and we attract sometimes
What we don't want and we should be attracted what we want
and so
There are but there are ways of you know cleansing yourself, you know
We're all full of sin
You want to put it that way sin, but we can be also in Buddhism they call it merit. There's like this like the opposite of sin
It's like doing good things
You know with the opposite of sin. It's not just doing good. It's like doing doing good for others. I'm doing good for the world leaving like a
And I think we can make up for like a lot of the bad we've done by doing good I do believe that
But not a lot of people want to like want to people a lot of people are are just happy
No, no, no, no, no, okay. I got it. I got a poor thing. I'm sorry
Catches that driving me nuts
Hey Rudy
Okay, much better now. I think we'll be knocked over
Japanese soaking tub that's that's done very nice. You know we have nearby we have a sensory deprivation text
This was like that in my bath it came with a little fortune
it says someone behind the scenes is deciding on whether to be an ally or an enemy. It has 183.
The number is 183. I don't know. That could be a hint. I just wanted to share that with you.
If anybody knows 183, has any relevance or any idea. Someone behind the scenes is deciding
Never use enough allies
Enemies seem to be plentiful
The fortune was for that guy sniffing their bikes I said it's the way
Who it might be I don't know maybe their birthdays January 1983 or something Capricorn, maybe
Or maybe 318 March 18th, but if you
The fortune was for the guys sitting sitting the bike seat. No
He was for me
It's always better to have a have an ally especially it's good to make your enemies your allies actually
It breaks into three a numerology. Okay. Yeah eight nine nine seventeen eight nine ten eleven twelve
Yeah, so two plus one is three, right?
Yeah
Yeah, so
Interesting we got
But I'm sure the number of creation. Yeah. Well, they're saying saying like you know the most evil number is number two
Because one is this number of unity and then two breaks off the unity into a duality
And so that and that creates the evil because otherwise everything is all good or is all
It was me you're an ally now. Oh, you were decided whether to become an enemy or ally. Wow
Well, thank you. I'm glad you became an ally
Yeah, there aren't any evil numbers, but the good and bad
Yeah, I don't I know there's not evil numbers, you know, two is the divine feminine. Yes. I mean, I've heard I've heard
Explain different ways, you know
When is masculine, yeah
To you know to dose. What does it do though?
Oh no, oh
Court
Yeah
Well, I've done I've done a lot of reading about numerology
Also, Jim Atria. I don't know if you guys have studied Jim Atria
Jim Atria is kind of like the study of
It converts a word to like a letter, you know, so like, you know, you can do it simply there's
different values in different systems, but I like just to do the straight, you know
There's 26 letters in the alphabet. And so that's gonna be you know
So let it's letters me one through 26. So like for example, the number w is 23
The number q is 17 the number j is 10
the number
You know a is one a one b two c three until we go c c c or that can mean there over go cc
That means 33, right?
So you can go to Jim matrix and type in your name, and it will show you all these
All these uh words that correspond to your name, so I can I can try to do something I can go
Look at it I can tell you like mine if you tape type my full name, which I won't tell you my full name
but
I'll type it in here, and I'll tell you the correspondences. So this is called Jim matrix org
Okay, there's if you calculate gematria
So for my name my number is 1213. So it says decode prepare yourself Baltimore Ravens. It says
5000 it says I'm not crazy
It says webmaster
Yankovic says Ron Howard wears Nemo what to do
Mark Howard
September 11 God hosts arrive Howard moon halloween night a scarecrow Corvus
Shawn Mendez he's like the wind black sky black death music that's one of the
thing and then Marilyn Monroe Hillary Clinton here comes the Sun ritual
cryptography Biblical prophecy Jade the female Christ
Sacred twin flames apocalypse island extreme arrogance you have to go by Celtic. Thank you for being here
So if anybody wants me to like
Look up their name or if you want to tell me even just like, you know your nickname I look up
Hey there spunky
Hey, there's spunky, okay
It says Jeffrey Epstein, uh-oh
Listen to the voice of God
It says
We're back, baby
special delivery I
Was a I w a z I was I know that name Queen of wands
Love her and her daughter
Decode tomorrow says white Persian cat snoop poop dog is evil
cute is wise a
sealed puzzle
Prepare yourself Lord Jesus Christ intergalactic travel the rising Phoenix glitch in the matrix
Ready for departure
Master the future subconscious mind
You found me QAnon, Apollo, Parnopoulos, Illuminati Mutant, Hazing Executions, Largest Woman Hater, How Great Thou Art.
I don't know. I mean, this is weird things. How are we doing, guys?
You're number 31. That was nice. Are you 31, Nick?
I can search Nick Johnson next if you want and you see Nick Johnson
So Nick Johnson
It says
Vesper, Sadism in Pyromania, Secret Society, Spear of Destiny.
I am the Code by Han K. God, Son of Yeshua, Manipulating Scumbags, God Returns on Earth,
You Are Not Dead, The Spectrum of Color, Holy Shit Moment, Run Spot Run, Peace is the Prize,
Tricia Paitas and Levitate. Also, Phoenix Coin, Princess Diana, Stronghold, The Divine Child, Walt Disney, The Most High, Archangel Azazel, The Rapture, The Living God,
Furniture, Yeas Yet Jesus, Flower of Life, Eminem in America, I've Got a Big Gun, God in the Flesh, Bartholomew. That's interesting.
So who wants to give their name because I do these urban dictionary urban dictionary names so I can do Nick
I'll read Nick's first and then everyone give me your first name if you want just Nick
A man with great power over most people, he can influence people to do what he wants.
He's trustworthy, girls want him, guys want to be him.
He has great ambitions and loves people for all ages, cultures, races, will not judge
you for what you do, but for who you want to become.
He often gets hurt and has a great heart, treat him with respect, he deserves that much
from you."
Aww.
That's a nick.
Anybody else want to have their name analyzed?
That's good spicy
Oh
Stephanie let's see
Okay
Stephanie
Yo, oh big L dough
I was just going to read about Stephanie real quick.
It says, Stephanie, the queen, the true goddess.
Her name says it all.
She's crowned, beautiful, honest, funny, loyal,
very lovable, but not good at showing up.
Beautiful inside and outside.
She's fire.
No one compares to her.
She's really one of a kind.
Stephanie's are quiet, but once you get to know her,
she's loud and fun to be around.
She hers, but will never show.
Don't get her mad, she will definitely show it.
A wild, free spirit child loves nature, adventure, animals, gets dirty, including in bed.
That's when you feel the real fire.
Has a unique case for expensive stuff.
But lazy to work for it to give her with no hesitation drops everything to be there for you
Love a Stephanie because there's no other like her
He's once in a lifetime brutally honest, but worth it her love for you grows only stronger
Once you fail her it's over with don't tell her what to do to only tell you what's best for you from the bottom of her
Oh step you just can't be without her
How is that?
Yeah, I read yours up before elbow. It said it said your video a dildo on your elbow or something remember that
Yeah, so I'm gonna build those
Yeah
My name, you know for a little bit, but it's alright
So have you been held up? I heard you were like saying that you're not gonna be my show or something
But Sam and are you both?
If someone's saying this morning, they said I'm discord you're saying you're gonna your boycotting my show or something
Are you lying?
No, I said why are you lying? I never said that. No, I know I know you did well someone told me told me you did
I
Don't want to I'm not trying while I'm working
Until I get off work cuz I got a new mic I paid for it, so I want to be able to use it
You know
But then I get bored, you know
It's better if I just wait until I get off of work because if I'm on when I'm while I'm driving then I'm on late
I ain't gonna want to do it all. I mean, so
Rather just get on when I got this my mic sound good, right? Yeah
You know when I can use this mic Arthur said it but so Arthur was lying. So is Arthur trying to cause trouble
Yeah, we're all good
Yeah, actually
Yeah, because I mean good. I got about like the past few days. I got about 20 memberships. That's pretty exciting and
Um, and thank you. Thank you so much to you. Um, you know, Dougie Doug, I know the Dougie Doug is really cool
I don't know if you ever met him
You know the elder would say that say what of Samantha. Oh
Yeah, oh, yeah, elder would say that he wouldn't be here on the show. I know I know
Elder elder though
It was Arthur you gotta watch
But I never said that, you know, I was on same man's a couple days ago
And I told him I was gone cuz he asked me why I don't go live anymore
I'm like shit get old man, you know, then I'll be working and I'm not trying to be driving and host lives
You know, I just rather damn panel, you know, it's easier
It's easier that way
Yeah, oh, you see today's pretty crazy like we had surgery diamond
Raging demon it beat on panel
Yeah, yeah
And I seen it I seen I was able to talk to flirty and
Raging I I definitely don't fuck with raging now
I mean and not because really if he is gay he's gay, but the fact that he just denies it
You know he denies the he don't he don't he don't respond to it. He just that he just tries to
Go on to another topic instead of responding to the question, you know, so I mean
Well, I mean, I mean, but he's I mean to say he I think he said he's dating being her and so obviously everybody knows
Yeah, I think they're they're watching their movies together about Titanic yesterday, you know, she's apologized for
For sharing his dick pic with the world, you know, we now evolved. Did you see his you see his wiener? I'm Elzo
No, no, I didn't see it. I seen the balloon. I've seen the edited version. Why is the string you're never connected hold on
Okay
stream
Because apparently apparently it's it's apparently his penis is big it's uncut he had a very big smile on his face
In the picture. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you seen it. Yeah
So, I mean, yeah, maybe if Frillardy and him break up,
maybe you get a chance with him.
You know, you just don't have to, you know, he might roll down.
I don't know.
Y'all can sort of fight, you know?
Sort of fight?
Have you heard of docking?
Yeah, I'm saying that.
I can see it happening.
Have you heard of docking?
No, what is that?
No, it's where it's where it's where I like put my penis on raging demons penis and then pull his foreskin over both the both of them
What the fuck?
That's what it is
You would do some shit like that. That'll that'll turn you on
maybe
Oh, y'all so y'all come over that cover. That's too much. That's too much at that point, man
You go, what is it called docking? I'm at the ass raising if I'm gonna catch them on panel
You're gonna dock with with with with flirty or sight. Yeah
My eyes man
It's a Chinese finger Chinese finger trap kind of thing
With dick. Oh, yeah. I know what that is. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Do you think man flirty can do her thing and
Call it a day, man. Call it a fucking day, man. But you see Kate right now because I think beta with Barry now, you know
So or Barry
Yeah, so Kate Kate, you know doing some wild shit right now and
Yeah, man, that's how the things go man. We back on this shit
You know
Yeah, we're cool like she wasn't we're she's on panel today, you know
You know raising demon, of course, you know always brings up, you know insults and stuff like that, but I just try to like
Look pat like this thing. I just want the show to like, you know people
I don't want like do you rail the show versus like some stupid thing something someone says I wanted I wanted them to like talk and like
It's everything so
But uh, okay over here too. Yeah, he was here
He was on with flirty at the same time, you know, and then they're kind of he's kind of professing his love and
No, oh my god, I missed a lot. Yeah, I'm telling you when I
Yeah, I don't miss the lot man. I mean I've been hearing what's been going on
But raging professed his love the flirty. That's a wild shit
Yeah, I'm raging raging you he's desperate. That's how desperate he couldn't get a female. He moved on to a young male
Well, you know
We're identifiers female, so
Well, I mean
Identify not she's still got a fucking sword
Right. Yeah
Yeah, they can have a sword fight. That's a beautiful. I mean he not gonna be able to put his dick in in the pussy or nothing
Right. Oh, that's what that's what the butthole is for. I
Guess right
Maybe convinced flirty that you know, he has money
Well, he says he's very highly unlikely, but you know, I think he said is he say he's very wealthy and we're he said
He called everyone else poor. He almost all poor in the image. He's so wealthy that he's on the internet
professing his love to a fucking male to him to men
That's how much that's how that's all in America. He's so wealthy. He can't find somebody over there in the UK or wherever
It shows confidence at least at least even he's confident about something there
Lordy and then he finds love with a fucking prostitute basically right or well, I mean the blade is
Yeah, the blow the blade is yeah the blade it but you know, she's a sex work, but I
Told her she should just do straight internet. This is just beyond the internet. It's like blood blood safer than
That's what she's telling people but she can be on the internet
She can be on the internet and make money off the internet. Nobody fucks with her like I mean she can try I guess
She could try yeah
She's trying to make money on the internet
I mean, no, no, she can't. I mean, it's like, you know, I mean, I can make money on the internet
Florida Diamond can make money on the internet. It's like, you know, but she can be on like, you know, like a web webcam site
You know under the the trans section and there's gonna be a lot of people. They know they're getting in trans there
They're just want to sit in chat. Basically, they'll do things for you know, like some tokens and donations for private shows
And so I just it's a lot better than walking around the streets. I don't know I do worry about
Safety and not disturb it all all trans people
All right, we can't forget that she tried to trick people too, you know, and you was here for it
You know, so what if she tries to do that again and tell people she's a man? What's good Nancy?
Yeah, transform is number one. Yeah, isn't that interesting? It's like there's you know, if you look at the number one
Uh, the number one popular type categories of porn, you know, people would think americans are pretty perverted, you know
it's got
You know black black dicks on white chicks and come fart cocktails and
You know dog fart
Whatever that that studio is black eyes and
Crazy so yeah, this is a romantic. Hey, it's a Nancy. Say hi. What's up, Nancy? Look at all the members thing that isn't a member
I don't think all of us, I think, I think his memberships expired, but Samantha, Spunky,
we got a lot, we got a lot of members in the chat though, I love seeing that.
Everybody coming back here because I guess she's robot and over there, but shout out
to the members, man.
We get cake first, that's the best, oh gosh Archie, oh Coke, Coke or cake, I can't, Coke,
Oh, yeah, dog part is like the name of a the name of a porno company
What a gay porno company it's not gay. No, it's like it's like a straight. It's like it's like usually it's like
Well, they do have like some cuckold videos where it's like
It gets kind of gay, but
They're mostly like this, but it's like it's like black guys gang-banging
Like a white chick
What's your what's your what's your favorite one to watch all of it?
Rado, I don't have a favorite
You know what I mean? I'll be honest. I don't have a faith. I mean I do but it ain't you know, it's random
You know just random you ever give her give her watch trannies
No, I do not watch that
Never looked it up. None of that if I ever if I ever run across some shit like that
I keep it pushing now, you know, you just do just change the channel
If I ever run across, you know to two guys sword fighting on a porn shit
I just keep it moving. I'll watch none of that. Okay, you wouldn't watch it
Guy I mean not guys
I mean you wouldn't even be able to tell them till they turn around and you thought it would just look like a normal
Normal females, but the Canada stress lesbian not trans. Oh, okay
Yeah, Canada Australia with lesbian United States. I think it's not is it obsessed with the trans now
What's your favorite Oliver? I'll like who likes the double penetration
Maybe it's on there, but I think overall transform is number one. Yeah, it's crazy
And I know like teeth and teenage porn to like, you know teenage
That's like a one of the top categories, too
Yep, let's see
That was everybody shout out your favorite type of porn in the chat. No, see well, I can watch I really don't like
Gay porn is like too much kind of too much for me. Almost it's like about feet
I was all of us into the feet of foot the feet fetish foot fetish, right?
Oliver likes to watch like women popping balloons with their feet and like pouring like whipped cream all over the feet and stuff, right?
No
It was not it was not sharing so
I have been drawing pictures of people I can draw. I'll draw another one of you, but I can't look I have my
Book around what you've been doing. Have you done any IRL?
Have you gotten any fish tacos? Have you walked the boardwalk or?
Whatever I just I just I just wrote a liquor store. I picked up some drinks and then I went got a subway sandwich
It's a pepperoni a honey
Hi hot, honey pepperoni sandwich is really good
delicious
Just hanging out with the chatty chat been doing some readings. You can do a lot of readings had good panels
Everything's going good
Yep
We wait wait wait, yeah, what is number one you went to subway?
Well, we had a good day today. It's a good day like over a hundred people in the chat today, Rado
So it's like the chat was picking back and now it's back down to like 15
But you know, you know, we go through different numbers or different people on
The more the people you get the better the more the content flowing the better
You know the more get because people come over to watch that fuck shit
Yeah
So
I mean, I'd like to see a psych versus beta, you know, so she's a fake-ass bitch, but I guess
You're very forgiving individual, you know
I mean
I don't like the fact she was talking about, you know, you then she started talking about jamie and
You know, she she she tries to make people choose sides and shit
You know, that she tried to kiss ass and manipulate you and no, I wouldn't do that. I'm looking for them
I'm I want I want I want the best for you psych. She don't want the best for you. She want the best for her
Well, you know one of these days you won't realize that shit, man
She wanted me to kick off 30 diamond and region D, man
I didn't know what I was saying. She's trying to control your shit
And if she don't get what she wants, she'll start her own shit, you know
Bragg about how she get better viewers and is that in a third like come on
Jamie I'm just speaking facts man. I
Was literally about to go up there. I was I was typing in her chat earlier
You know me because I just found it funny that Kate was in the chat
Mad, you know spurting at that that Barry was up there. She tried to get beaded to kick Barry off
I just found that funny as fuck
You know, so, you know, I had to type in the chat, you know, but um
While she had her own panel going so Kate live and then she's she's pissed off that uh
She's actually and she's doxin beat at that. You know, she's doxin be the right now
so
What's crazy gotta be careful cuz be the mice, you know, if you got Kate over here again be the might bring that up
You know, you need to you need to ban Kate because she was doxin me
Know well, I really am not on other people's channel. I don't see I mean I trust people's word for but
As long as they don't do it here
you know, this is a place to hash out stuff not to like
Carry on
There's stuff from different. Yeah, so people are saying the number one categories are like trans teenager and mature
I mean a year
That's like one of the top categories. Yep teenager
What up Jonathan my slow haggle right there, man. We've been around for a minute man
You know ETC days ease the crane days section eight days
I'm off of the price still over there too slow ass
Come on Nancy, let's let's let's move on from that tran porno shit
Let's talk about how weird raging demon is, you know
well
He was saying like
You know terrible things like threatening. He said he was gonna go
He's gonna find us all one by one and hunt us down and stuff. I
Mean, I mean, I'm just saying but I mean trying to date this thing here, you know, so oh my god
Oopa-loop. I'm just saying
Who's that flirty flirty
I guess I'm not sure. I just happened to find it in this board, you know?
Oh
How do you say friends? Yeah
Yeah
We used to be affiliated back in the day like a year ago. Has it been a year yet? I don't know
He's the one that's moved in with pebs after saying that, you know
It's crazy man. He fell off man. He fell off so bad that he had to move in with peps
Pebs moved in with him to try to do better for herself. She had to go move in with a roommate with a chatter
And I guess Zaya was invited to move in with them too. So now he live over there, you know
Well, he spends the his last days, you know
trying to revive his channel, but
That shit ain't going nowhere. Do they all sleep in the same bed? Oh
Pabs in Zaya
That's what I heard how you know that's what I heard that's been a talk doesn't sleep in the same bed sleep in the same room
I mean who knows how many rooms jade got damn
Okay, they can't do it
Doug don't tell me Kate did it man. Does she do it to herself?
No, I'm not helping that nigga out man. He doesn't he don't he need to help himself out
He need to sell them sneakers and try to revive his fucking channel. I
Don't live off the internet, you know, I don't depend on the internet to pay my bills
I don't even go over there no more, you know, I don't go I don't go over to shit
I haven't been in his discord in a minute
I don't fuck with that nigga, man. I don't fuck with his channel. Sometimes I'll pop in and
And if a live pops up on my YouTube other than that, that's it rarely pop up anymore
like the pepshiddle pop up, you know
but
The pepshiddle pop up here and there and I'll go over there and try to troll her but other than that
I don't fuck with I don't fuck with him. I don't be around
Uh allegedly be this calling the law on Kate for doxin
That bitch drunk as hell. Can you imagine how big be the sound calling the police right now? Hello?
Burping and shit cuz she's so fucking drunk. I'm being I'm being doxxed on the internet
I just drunk a bottle of motherfuckin' liquor and I'm just calling you to tell you I done
got dicks and I can't even see straight because I'm so fucking drunk at three o'clock in
the fucking afternoon or four o'clock in the afternoon.
Come on man, fuck that, fuck that hole man.
Somebody need to record her calling the police, hopefully she put it on speaker, I need to
Yeah, everything's okay. Let me see. Hell nah, Chung ain't helping him out. Chung slow himself.
Juice, I don't know. Juice might help that motherfucker. Toss might help.
Toss might help Zaya. Juice might help. Tony D2 Wild might help Zaya. He did it to himself though,
you know, to keep it a hundo.
He wanted the trolling to stop the trolling brought in the majority of his fucking money and it killed his fucking business
The trolling brought in the majority of his money even before a
Lot of people that's in there now was in there because back in the day when he was fucking going back and forth with skinny
A lot of people used to bring in troll donations. They used to troll donate all the time
After he's banned every troll he tried to now he's more lenient because you know, he see that shit don't work
But uh, yeah, man, what it is man, you're gonna have to get in on the five if he ain't already getting on the five
Smokey fuma the Glazer you say you'll drop my link
Hey, I don't even I don't even smokey. Oh smokey Fuma here. He probably help
I don't see smokey like that. He might be over there with they a lot, but I don't see him like that
He a family man
Chunk kicks out of membership, so
Sam in this weekend too
Yeah, Chunky there he is right there Chunky man. I said you I said your slow ass ain't helping gay man
That's what I say. You got a problem with that Chunky if they ever needed to help you you wouldn't help him
What you gonna give him a pair of fucking sneakers?
That's what I say. You got problem with that shit
ETC going downhill papa
Jamie just posted your channel elder. There's big elders channel appreciate that appreciate that. Yeah. Yeah appreciate that man
Man, my channel was popping man not that see my channel never died off man
I just chose to stop going live because I got bored, you know
Like right now if I were to go live my shit would probably have the same amount of yours as you because I ain't been live like that
But I'm good. It's more of a panel man. That's I'm good with that man. I don't need you are remount. You're
Remonetized, that's pretty good. You know, so yeah, I'm on it. I still I did get remonetized
That means you put at least like you know a lot of a predictor channel. You got thousands of hours. You got a thousand subscribers, so
You know I got monetized when I have 500 view. It was like 500 like 17
Subs when I got monetized people's like it cuz I think people say usually get monetized when you got like 700 800
But I got that shit when I think I think
KK got monetized on her second channel. She got like five something
Yeah
It's possible to get monetized early like with with like four fires or at least five hundred subs
I think it's a for me was
It was a thousand subscribers and three thousand watch hours for me to
Yeah, if you go and you go a lot guys if you do live you know if you do have panels there's gonna be a lot of people on the panels
Have there's a lot of people coming for the people on the panels. It's gonna be yeah rato got me monetized
He just got remodeled right?
I believe he did I believe he did
No one copied Gaia. Everyone done what Gaia does is slow Chung
Okay, yeah Chung as a member guys if you guys want to become a member
Have access to like a lot of
Nick I think how the fuck I copy is a I don't my my my content does not revolve around how they do his content
My shit is off of people arguing back and forth
Chunky what everybody's doing now
So what do you mean, man?
I'm not gonna say I didn't come from over there as a chatter. Yeah, you know
So it says for Nancy, I'm just saying he fell off man
He the reason he fell off and I said this shit before he fell off that his demise was coming because of what he was doing man
This is Nancy it says Nancy Nancy's a person who loves and cares for her friends family and partner
She's very pretty caring smart sincere person. She'll always be truthful and trustful
You're always relying her Nancy's really nice caring person when she finds the one she will love him forever
When she says you're the one you know, she loves you Nancy's a nice friend
She'll treat you good and care for you no matter what Nancy will be the best friend in the world
She's very funny. She'll make you laugh and you're upset will help you with any problems you have
She's incredibly cute without any makeup on
She's stunning without even trying. Nancy loves to help people out with anything, no matter what it is, and she'll try her very best.
Oh, Roto, your last live was fun. Yeah, I remember the last live, although it was shaking his butt. It was great.
Yeah, and then I lost it because of fucking Smelly. Dumbass Smelly because of a picture.
What is a smelly put a picture of oh smelly. No, I had a picture of smelly up there
And it only I only had it up there for like 15 seconds, bro
and
She ended up fucking privacy striking me
It don't matter smelly. It don't matter
The fucking picture was up fucking 15 seconds 10 seconds not even that long
You got rid of a whole fucking eight-hour the whole day's worth of a live
Why do you think I don't need one? What's the point of going live if people like fucking Smully gonna get mad?
No
Really, so they were half dying in the picture you posted your post
The only reason the only reason the only reason the pictures out was because of your ass
No, he never takes me back. Doug. He never takes me which which which has me thinking and that's really his number
So I'm not gonna give up on it when I go live or I'm gonna end up calling him one day when I'm when I'm on a live
Or when I'm live
But I never got a text back so
Who smelly smelly right there in the chat on it
I'm not trying to hear that shimaly you disappoint me man
You disappoint me shimaly. That's all I'm gonna say man. You disappoint me man
I and I and be even before that I wasn't even going live. It's been months since I've been live
I go live finally and
Shimaly clapped their lives
God damn
And really I mean I don't really give a fuck but it's like it gives me reason not to even go live
And there's got to be something going on for me to go live too. That's why I keep telling people I'm not in the mix like that
I'm not in the action like I used to be
So it makes it hard for somebody to go live you got to have some type of drama going on
Which typically starts in discord, you know, so thank you Jamie, I appreciate you
Yeah
You ain't listen
Listen, I convinced kiss my cheeks to take a panel. I don't know she's ever been on a panel
But I was asking her to join panel like fucking I was asking every time I seen her as a finally she joined this shit
So who that George was good George Wallace. What's good my good? Is that George Wallace? I might be wrong man
What's good Nicole man? I
Might be wrong
My bad my bad. I might be wrong. Oh
You've been on psych's panel. All right, so why are you on join? Like you ain't got to turn your camera on like what you so scared of
What you sound weird
But hey, I don't get it. I don't get it, man
Especially when you you know, you're a part of what's going on at times. I
Love to hear what you got to say about Kate man for real Shimeli
One of these days man, one of these days you got a joint panel
Are we doing a chat guys? Let's see case. Oh, okay. It's one day. I'll be
Kali he had the midget hose her off in the backyard. Oh my god
What what just happened? Oh
You have more information about that
How's everyone doing? Oh
It's a it's a quiet day today, huh?
It's like I mean I know you quiet people are earlier, but it's part they're like a hundred
They're like a there are hundred people in here earlier. She's like, you know, it's gonna quiet and
Yo smelly if you ever decide to do it, I got you man. You got control. Listen listen smelly
If you decide to do it one day, but I got to build my shit up
I don't want to do it like like I have to know I have at least 50 60 people on the chat
But if you ever trying to do that man
And let's go for really anybody that I know bring content like
Like I wouldn't just bring anybody on panel you give what I'm saying to try to like double team you shit like that
But I'd like to hear what you had
Even if you go on anybody panel it really don't need got to be my shit
But I'd like to hear what you got to say about Kate, you know
Because you and her were closer than me and her was I think so
It's crazy cuz I ain't really never turn on that fucking bitch until you know, I
Said what I said on Sam and panel, you know
But uh, when she started fucking with somebody like she doing now, you know when she was started fucking with somebody I fuck with you know
And uh, but prior to that I was tight with Kate man
Everyone good chat. Let's see. I have defended her for the past year
Well, I don't know. Yeah, Kate. I heard Kate was talking about my father and stuff like that and then she came in
She's like, I'm not talking about I'm not saying stuff about you. So I don't know. I haven't been there. I know
She even docks be the dad and be the chat earlier psych
Kate was docks and be the dad. That's why I try to tell people people need to open her eyes
If y'all gonna hate me trying to call me a doctor and shit
Y'all need to look at Kate cuz she fucking coin docks her
Her and pebs hold the title as as female queen dox is my
Yeah, and I try this because she I didn't even know be this dad named till today
Yeah, yeah Nancy, I don't know y'all ain't y'all ain't see that half of y'all had to see it
Kate fucking Docs be the dad because
Beta didn't even do shit. I don't fuck with beta, but I'm still gonna cause shit down the meter
Got down the middle. The only thing beta did was have Barry on panel and fucking Kate started Docs and fucking beta
How does that make sense?
Y'all gotta talk to me. How does that make sense, bro?
You get what I'm saying
All all be today was have Barry on fucking panel
And and I got to learn fucking beat a dad name today not that I wanted it
But I'm just saying I got to know what his name is cuz a fucking Kate
Just saying man
Yeah
What if you if you don't like Doc's and Nancy you gotta watch just watch Kate
If you piss Kate off enough, she will fucking dox people that and she talked about me and her fucking nephew
Right her nephew is a fucking a
Football player, you know I'm saying so it's like I'm not saying I'm totally right
But at the end of the day Kate not Kate not innocent, man
Hey, not innocent man, you know what I mean
You look Boris like how long you've been
Yeah
I'm good. I'm just a drinker. I have I'm just looking pot. I have this like this vape. Where's my vape? Oh
Here this look got a vape elder look oh
Shit, oh they got weed in it
That's what got not that I don't smoke though, but I'm just saying that's crazy they're making vapes like that
博士
Yeah, it's like it's like we should just like not talk
I mean we can leave you can say anything we want on the internet
But it's like let's like not get personal with people so it's not refillable. No, these are like they're all in ones
I got three of them for like 60. They're like so that's 20 bucks a piece for like their grand cartridges
They're she's a go for 30 to 40 bucks. So so so I'm just saying if I gave you 50
You gonna let me call Kate Berger on your on your live or not if I give you $50, you know, let me do what?
Can I call somebody on your life like a call?
Yeah, and I call somebody while you're live and everybody can hear if I give you 50 bucks
It don't matter what yeah, you don't you say yeah
You say yeah
I gotta confirm. That's the number though, but I would do it. Okay, what's I think chat?
Let me know what I think
Um, I'm so
Say yes
Love looks like what that money he don't give a fuck about who it is, but he's not stupid psych not done
Oh shit, and I got a screenshot smelly
of somebody else or not this is me okay I see where I did it but somebody else was
using your picture I forget who Pinot was though it might have been KK
Pinot I might be wrong though I don't know KK was on the other day
oh yeah she came on the panel you were you were are you with her up she was
here they can juice it was a juice world was in the chat and like you and KK
KK was on for a while. She was had a hot shit out picture of the hot dog in her mouth. Oh
Yeah, yeah, that's KK
Yeah, KK was on here
Damn, I'd be missing a lot, bro
Yeah
Kiki was here. Let's see
I'm addicted to this fucking audio book too man. Like we listening to
Oh shit a snake. Oh, that's not a fucking snake. I
Thought I was a snake man. What the fuck
You know I'm saying this motherfucker had a anaconda number, but yeah, we what are you listening to an audio? Oh
Yeah, yeah, yo, I'm addicted. I'm addicted to this one audio book. I think I already told y'all it's on um
It's on this app right called pocket F
It's a it's a it's on this app called pocket fm bruh
But the thing is it's expensive man. Like after they'll give you like a couple they'll give you like a
Couple like a chapters
Not even chapters. They'll give you a couple
I guess chapters for free and after that they charge fucking a lot man
Like for the rest of the chapters and shit, that's the only thing I don't like
But other than that it gave me through my day, man, so if anybody like reading books man
I've been on all the bull. I've been on a lot of different ones, right?
Ain't nothing compared to pocket FM. Oh
I don't even like I'm not even a reader like that matter of fact, you know, I'm saying not like that
It's people that read that like to read way more than I do
But they got some good-ass books on on that uh, on that up, man
and if anybody know how to get them fucking uh, if anybody learn how to get
Them audio books on pocket FM for free like if there's a way to like download them shits
Like like people do like new movies and shit. Let me know man
I'll toss y'all a couple dollars because I'm spending a lot of money, man
I'm just saying I'm just saying
Yeah, cuz cuz you know you never know psych, you know, it could be a chatter that be on there and figured out a way to get
Them chips for free
Pirate no, listen if you figure it out thing that is
If you figure it out TT, I'm gonna call you TT. That's that's too long for me. Have you figured that out TT?
And you can find
Shit that's on pocket FM cuz what's on pocket FM isn't on audible y'all so they not stupid
So if you can uh, you said pirate
I'm gonna have to look into that man
Cuz if this whole time I've been spending fucking hundreds of dollars and this whole time I could have got this shit for free
I just ordered everyone's gonna be really happy. I would I just ordered I just ordered I was like a 60 piece
Like that. Yeah. Oh, what would you talk about? I'll cut you off man. What would you talk about? What is that?
See it's like it's like a nail kit about about this for like my nails
Oh, yeah, you ain't pay a lot because you know, your ass cheap as hell.
Oh, you said pirate. Hey, how's, oh, okay, I'm gonna look into it right now.
Matter of fact, while I'm on here, I could do it because I'm on my Macbook.
Shout out to the Macbook.
I remember I got this with me and KK when, I mean, not KK when Kate was my co-host and shit back in the day.
Before burying shit was all my shit like a lot
It was Kate Kate was on my shit a lot and I got this MacBook. Let me see
So what do you mean? Is it pirate calm? I don't get it
What's up? What do you mean chat?
Is it pyre?
You're saying pirate Rodo is a pirate radio is a good plan words. Oh, man. What the fuck man?
So what are you talking about?
Oh, Jamie. Oh, my girl. KK right
there. Can you pin KK chat or KK?
Yeah, chat. That's my girl.
That's my girl. Isn't that?
Yeah, she got to work on the lip though. She got to work on that top lips like
She love me
Lisa loves to do. Yeah, I've seen Alisa wear like a whole outfit
It was a glasses and like a dark glasses and a dress and she's like well
I got this from spinning the wheel at Timu and for free
So she knows how to do I I've been trying to figure out that super wheel at Timu for who you talking about
Alisa. Yeah, she loves Timu
Chelsea lives Ross she loves forever 21. She loves that but she loves a good deal and
She's like she doesn't like to spend too much money on clothes. She likes to get a good deal on clothes
She looks good in everything
Yo, uh, y'all talking about pirate radio calm like what do you what are you trying to say Jamie?
Cuz I can't I type in pirate radio. Hold on
It's not even spelled like the way you spelled it. Let me see man. Y'all gonna get me fucking
Nah, y'all gonna have to give me a link or something man cuz I
Look I look that it's not coming. It's not coming up. No, that's not Jamie. That's not the real cake. I was just playing
That's not the real KK
That's a all that's somebody fucking with her
Wait, is that KK?
Well, I think that is I don't think that's KK KK. That's you right me in your discord. I don't think that's KK
I think somebody fucking with her
I don't know I think they were trying to tell you with a good joke
They're saying pirate rado instead of pirate radio. They said pirate rado. They're trying to get recommend anything
But that sandwich was good I
Know I think he was like saying KK with somebody else. I don't know. I don't know. I'm very confused guys
Yeah, I don't think that's cake
I don't think that's good. Okay, so Jamie says there is a pirate rado radio. Let her look
Jamie can post the link actually so if she finds something she can post the link
Oh
Damn, I guess be the listening. Oh, nevermind
I don't know what's going on right now, man.
I
Got me by me. Give me a minute. I mean, I'm gonna ban the word jelly for my chap
Wow, and you say it this is some big pipes ruined it for everybody
Yo, what happened to Alex and what happened to Alex like Alex still join all the mother easy stop joining like
Wow. No, I mean, this is, this is your, this is your joints all the time. And Alex says, I don't know. Does Payne still join? Does Payne still join? Yeah, Payne, Payne's here today. She's like, she, she, she yelled at people.
Yeah, I know she'd be joining like early morning, like 12 in the morning or something. I guess she, her time zone is like yours or something. I don't know.
He was but occasionally like I'll I'll bring him up because
The Tracy butterfly have you talked to that Tracy?
Yeah, I don't crazy. She's in here sometimes
She's doing good. You see I haven't seen you. I know I ain't really fucking with beat us
So, you know, but I fuck with you Tracy, you know, I know I was gonna agree with what I got to say about with beat up
But it is what it is
Michael was here this morning
You like Michael
No, I don't fuck with Michael man. He weird
He old Tracy like $800
Oh, you don't believe that you don't believe he old Tracy
And me yeah, you don't believe he old Tracy I'm asking you
Well, it's between them. It's like not my business
Yo, I can't believe a 40-some year old fucking UK motherfucker, it's fucking way
Yo same a joint real quick so we could talk about this thing on this weekend. It might have to be Sunday because I
It might have to be Sunday
But you got to talk to duchy y'all cuz he got the shit
My bad say what was you saying? No, we all good. We're good. I was just looking for my cigarette. There we go
Yeah, I mean, I I don't know what's going on with
Everybody but
I've been over here. What was your response to what I said? Well, I like that. I just I don't know something
I understand it's legal, but at the same time I
Fucking
Diamond is like 23 is some shit and he like 49 or some shit. Well, I mean
No, I mean they're both I mean 23 years old. I mean, there's there's a grandpa. He like a great. He like grandpa grandpa
Grandpa
Grandpa Arsenio, that's that's
Remember there's someone you remember someone named Arsenio Hall. Do you remember there used to be someone named Arsenio Hall?
And then the audience and the audience and bark they go
That's it wow
No cooking. Oh, so you know up here. So same man don't come up here unless you got more than like a hundred viewers or 50 or whatever
Ain't that a shame?
Nigga, I'm not it don't always got to be cooking my nigga. I'm up here chilling with fucking sight
Talking about what's going on right now
Like nigga, it ain't always got to be something cooking my nigga. That's that's how you know niggas be phony as shit
You can't even join a take a link unless there's fucking some type of drama going on that good. That's weird, bro
That's I'll be telling y'all man. I might I might go low and shit, but at least I keep that shit a hundred
I'm up here supporting site man
Like I'm just you know talking to him. We just talking about current events what he got going on
Oh my bad, I'm about to say I'm just saying I'm passionate make it don't be disrespectful dog
Yep, okay
Don't gotta be like drama for me to cook cuz if I only come when there's drama, bro, that's fake as hell
I'm just
If I only come over here when he got a hundred viewers, that's fake
I ain't got a problem coming over here when he got a couple viewers
That's that's how I started anyway when I was coming over here. He only had like fucking 15 viewers
Yep
Yeah, he does he does join me off to
Wait, that was a good sandwich guys. I finished out that sandwich. I don't fuck with subway. That was subway
You know was good
I forgot what it's called ma
What quiz knows jersey makes what?
jersey mites yeah jersey mites jersey mites got some good ass fucking
uh
They got some good subs yo
jersey mites got some good ass
Publix i don't think i got publics is
I didn't really got publics do i got is there a publics around that it might be
I ain't never tried Publix I never tried Publix I'm still kind of hungry though eat some cat food
man I'll give you $20 if you eat some cat food no how much how much for you to eat cat food like
To the fish
You wouldn't eat cat food I know a couple people that would what am I gonna Tommy James?
He bought that money
I'm not quite desperate enough yet
Savior to the shit show there's a song called the shit show SHYC. I think they won a
They won a membership yesterday, but they're live streaming, you know
So there's somebody does somebody give away 20 or did people start joining?
People start joining what what do you mean?
You said you got you said it was 20 members given yesterday. So did you yeah?
No, no, no, you you mean you donated some
Then um and then Doug Dougie Doug donated some and then I
Been last time I was like I was doing membership membership of summer summer donated
I mean, but then Jennifer Jenny Jen Jen girl. She uh
She bought a membership and some people about members of people it was just like it was just like a lot of stuff going on a lot of
Member highlights so people have been members for over a month. Thank you. I see Schmelly's in the chat
I got members here. Awesome guys. Oh, yeah, but Eldo
Big big supporter and a big helper give us initial memberships
So how many memberships you got how many total members you got right now?
Oh
I don't know. I think it's about maybe a hundred. I think it may be it may be probably maybe a little bit less
But uh, I mean it's at the most have had over a hundred members
You know and then you know a lot a lot of those were gifted the first month
But still you know, it's getting back up there. I think there's a
You know
Maybe it was this month. It was probably the last month. It wasn't as much as it wasn't as many there's lobster. Let me see lobster
Hi, Lenore
A lot for so expensive
Damn, why are you trying to take my content nigga?
And I don't even think smelly would take my shit, but at least you know
She come on man. Hold on man. I know Sam and ain't over here trying to y'all he be lurking bra
That's how we talked about a minute ago. Hold on
Come on though. Why you over here trying to steal my content if it happens to happen? Come on, man
You also bitch take a shit, man
No, I'm telling you, but oh, thank you, Jamie. I'm I'm I'm clicking on them. I appreciate you
You're saying man, you a funny motherfucker, bro
Tell them I have he was learning Schmeli this is Nick this man was fucking lurking. He was lurking Schmeli
And we talked about that like fucking 20 minutes ago
I
Supposed to have vegan too, but I'm gonna wait till something big happened with her
Did you see what happened with mr. Big Pipes?
I don't fuck with them. Yeah. Yeah. What what happened? I just don't fuck with mr
Well, what one night like one night I kicked him off the show and then I like brought him back later
And then he's like at your show and and then he started and we're bombing and then I had him back
And then I like bottom back because I said I ban him but I always like you know
He was back and so then he was using this like it's like sigil. It's like it's like a profile photo
But it was like someone's like oh, that's in chaos magic
He just got patted up and he didn't need to have it up because his camera works fine and so then I
Just say and then he was just talking weird and like it being really inappropriately sexual with me
So I like I just blocked him and then he came in my back chat
He was like I I'm putting a hex on you stick six six six and like saying all this like weird
Stuff and then he keeps trying to come back on but yeah, so he's off and you know, I
Don't know
Yeah
See so this whole time he was he was it's okay, bro
So this time he was doing some weird shit. Yeah. Yeah, he's trying to like he's trying to cast magical spells on me or something and then
Jamie's Cowboys. Thank you so much
Thank you so much Jamie
Yeah, I'm gonna see this
And I buy you membership I
Get well, I can't I wish I wish I could I wish I could
It's random, I don't even got a membership, but I give out memberships I could but I'm always watching
I'm usually here. So I got you
You get for members of what we have to do. Oh, if you go like follow this link Jamie. I think this might lead to it
There try that oh
Melly, thank you so much. Look at smelly gift in a membership. Thank you so much
Yo psych so so did you have to set up the ranking thing that shows up now in your chat?
the number one, number two, with the crown thing.
Did you set that up or started that?
I don't think I set up.
I have to figure out where to set that up.
Oh, I have to figure out where to set that up.
I do have to figure out where to set that up because.
So you did set that up.
I didn't, I didn't, but I know it's out there
because I've seen it on leases and a few other chats
and I just, I just haven't found like the,
I haven't found an exact place where you can set that up.
No, it's on your chat right now. It's there. The ranking is it who's ranked isn't
The XP is is on your shit right now
It is and people see it. I don't see it
Did you click did you add it or no, I must have I must have I must have
I gotta try to do it on mine if I ever go live again because it shows you I like it because it shows your top
Your top chatters and all that like I'm assuming is the top chatters. Is it the top? Yeah, you're top fans basically
That's crazy. Like the girl shade
Who is that she be typing?
Who shot?
Shosh I
Don't see the ranking though. I don't I don't see any of your ranking in much. Oh, yeah
I do it's number three Jamie's Cowboys number three. Oh, wow. Yeah number one is uh some girl
Nicole
Wait, but why is hold on is this shit? Why is it showing? Oh, it shows your ad
It's gonna end up showing your ad it's not gonna show the name. Damn. All right
Really, so that's Nicole. Yeah, that's Nicole. That's Nicole. Okay, so she's your number one
I don't know
It's whole it's with the hearts of it. So it's using your it's using people's ads and shit
Then holding is in here
Jimmy John same man. So same and don't donate so it has to do with people chatting
How same man above Schmeli Schmeli been typing more than have all y'all even basically. Oh
Person I haven't seen person in a minute. Oh, I like this yo
Yo, and I can do giveaways with shit like this. Yeah, there's a
Bedtime, I don't know how they get the how do you get I don't have people get points and that cuz man to Avery
They cha cha slide
Y'all like
That's it
Yeah, I like that because that because you can do you can
And you don't have to only support people that don't
or you don't have to like give away for people
that only donate, you can do it for everybody.
Cause it shows you who'd be like,
I guess who'd be typing and shit.
Like the most I'm assuming.
I don't know how that should work.
I like that, man.
I like that I ain't even gonna lie to you, man.
You're getting answers number eight.
You can do giveaway.
Well, you know, people can do giveaways, you know?
Samans number thirteen. I like that man. I ain't going to lie to you man.
I mean there's a lot of people tied for like you know there's like 75 points like you know
everyone like most people have 75 points I think if you just start typing the chat.
Is it per chat? Is it per live or is it overall?
I'm not sure. Because if it's per live it's going to make it hard.
I'm not sure. It's going to make it harder.
Oh, look at look at Lenore. That's Lenore. Are you happy? That's Lenore. Hi
I mean they trying to eat man, when was the last time you fed that cat, man? Oh, she's fine.
You been eating on the cat food or something? Chill out. No, she's fine. Lenore, are you happy?
She's just loving
All right, she said feed me man. She said why the fuck you not feed me man. Oh, please cats are fine
All right, damn
All right kitty cats
Yeah
Are they still protesting over there in California, I don't think so because I really haven't like heard much about it
It's crazy how it just disappeared. You know, I'm saying like
You know, cuz that's all they were talking about and then this Iran stuff happened where
You know the Iran shit happened where
Where the world was about to start in order and they stopped talking about the protesters
There's the money for membership okay, so Jamie wants me to use the money for membership, so
You know let's do it where Jamie wants me to use that money for memberships as well do a few do what?
Yeah, she sent me ten bucks. So she'd like me to
Send you know, maybe get a couple of memberships today. I'll do one right now
I can guys
Damn somebody got a new picture of fucking be the damn
Damn be the
Mitchell Mitchell got a membership. I don't know if Mitchell is a chat. Congratulations, Mitchell
Who got the membership y'all let me know chat let me know Mitchell who my name Mitchell
Mitchell where you at Mitchell
Mitchell
Yeah, I'm Mitchell's I got to Mitchell's one of the lurkers that caught your caught Mitchell
Recognize you but I bet you're around
They'll get an email saying that they got it. So
Yeah
They'll get that email. Maybe they'll start typing
I love it when
Yeah, so you have fruit. Okay
Yeah, Mitchell official got one. I'll do another one in a little bit, you know
Thank you, Jamie for donating. So, you know for the memberships, you know
Really appreciated it. You know, that's really cool. I love having a lot of green names in here
Shows people really really support the channel, you know, of course you get more cards and stuff like that
Yeah, I'm just thinking of new ideas of like you know things things to do with the show. I can make this
Oh, I really can't make this like an amazing show like this can this is still the humble beginnings of the show
I think I can have you know
It won't be the same when there's like like you know if there's a thousand people in the room as opposed to a hundred
It won't be the same kind of show, you know, and then but I'll still uh, I'll
Still uh, I won't forget my I won't forget my friends. I see so
So yeah, so I donated a membership. Mitchell got one. Oh, Christine. Thank you, Christine
Yeah, it's a membership extravaganza tonight. Thank you so much Christine Christine and oh bean gang we see the membership
There you go bean gang
Damn clumsy got a fucking membership
Let's you gotta remember
Members
using the chat
Oh
Guys that's fun. Thank you so much Christine. Hey Christine. Thank you. Smelly
It's a really fun win
We increase the members
Build them up to build them to family
Appreciate you guys love you guys so much. Yeah, I had my subway sandwich, you know, and I got my heart eliminates
Spunky I thought you were up. Thank you smelly. Oh my gosh
Thank you so much smelly
Yeah, this way. Oh, it's a Tom star. Tom star. I think I've seen Tom star in the chat today
Tom star
There you go guys at my cash out. Just let me know I'll post
We know what you laughing at dog. I'm serious man. I need some money
Well
I hear you well, I've been here if you don't want to become a member
I believe I believe in me
Yeah, if anyone wants to either give to membership or or join the membership you can just
Click on the dollar sign. It's on on iphone iphone where I have had unfortunately
It's on
Android we can be talking about
You got you got them good ears, huh?
It's exciting I want to I want to rule with the when things are you know, and there's like a
seems like you know, it's kind of like a
Little bit of energy right here. So, you know you want to
Okay, I'm gonna I'm gonna buy a I'll buy another membership. Okay, I'll do one more right now. Okay
As Jamie said, it's been, it's been, it's been, it's been on a gifting membership. It's okay. So I'm going to keep my word.
Yes, indeed.
Hey there, baby Ferrari. I thought I hate this one. Hey, there's one. He hasn't got more money. Oh my god
Yo, they're y'all hitting them with all that money. No, no, I said that one, but I really appreciate it guys
Let's see. I know that wasn't a casus. I was just my team being
But there we go. There. Yeah. Yeah. It's my couple of members for the day
Thank you guys for donating. Thank you Christine Smelly. We have a little membership drive guys. It really is awesome because
okay
really awesome because
You know, they just they help my channel a lot
Think that it look at bean gang. Look at bean gang as a member. There you go. Yeah, your name in green
Look at all the green names now guys. I want to like let's make it all green. Let's have it
Let's have like all you know all this almost never solve those numbers
Pretty cool guys. Thank you. And so with membership, it will get more cars. Thank you, Gotti. I believe that.
Yeah, oh Christine. Thank you so much. Okay
Not you got that one
Oh, they're molly molly molly nine
Congratulations. Thank you so much Christine
Love you. Thank you so much
Yeah, so I will do um. Oh, thank you dog. Thank you so much dog
Yeah, come on. Yeah, thank you here. I'm gonna give you a heart dog. There you go. Thank you so much
It helps you know, I want to I want to make this channel I want to
I want to succeed, you know, all my family has succeeded, everyone's succeeded in whatever they've done, you know, they all succeed.
I really want to succeed in this.
It would be great someday to have, you know, just totally, just my channel just totally being a success.
I just think that'd be awesome.
And I think I'm getting there. I go step by step.
I was like, I'm going to be myself.
Yeah, Doug D's a good guy.
Thank you.
Jamie, Doug D, some wonderful, wonderful people today.
Help me out.
But I hope you that I really hope you guys love this channel.
And this channel is for you as long as I'm here this channel will be here as long as I can have this channel up
you know and
For you guys to enjoy I want to make you I like to step back sometimes
I think you guys know you guys are all stars in your own right
You know if this is like a launching platform for you if this is like, you know the first place you go to to
you know and participate in panels really or if you're really really experienced and you just
you know like this panel and you just come in different forms yeah
so let's just have fun you know life is so serious life is difficult uh let's go here to like not
worry about that. Schmelly thank you so much and Dust Dog, Dust Dog received the membership I've
Yay people are yeah guys you have to like I don't know how the the point system works, but you know
Hold on what's going on at the point system? I think that uh you see the top bands look
There's Nick Johnson taking the lead with the 200 points
I'm not sure how you're doing it
How do you do that Nick? How do you gain points? Have a good stream sorry for the negative? Oh, it's okay
It's okay being gang
Thank you guys so much for the membership. That was sweet
It's really cool
Jamie's Cowboys, thank you for the donation. Awesome. I'm so nice man. I'm so nice man. She lose to the lose to the donators man
So lose to the donators man appreciate y'all the real ones free side donate free side don't be stingy same man
Don't be stingy dog
Be a real one dog
Mousey
Who's that on the screen that
What happened? Who's that on the screen? Oh
this this uh
The same man. Oh, it's a man. I thought the same man in the chat. Yeah, the same way showing this ding dong
But it's covered. You know me. Oh my gosh
That's big
You think so same man?
What's that has a nipple on it
Um, hey, yeah, what? Yeah, I don't know. Christine. I don't know. What's going on?
Sam and Sam and just Sam and just
Sam and please say I have the right to use the photo. Is that you say man?
This change it just change it. Just change it. Please. Okay. I'll change it. I'll change it. I'll change it
What about this one? Oh
Okay
That's the real one. That's the legit one
Well
At least he's I mean he's smiling
Okay, yeah
Wow
Well, yeah
Reggie demon he just looks so nice. I mean he has such a nice look
Yeah, yeah, he like he had looks like the real Arseneo Hall, you know, he's a senior
But he looks like Arseneo and it looks can tune it so much. He eats three meals a day
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, I didn't see the picture
This is playing naked twister
Did you see that no look but honestly you see beat us curved nail
Bear wet like a beat us curved now. Oh
She's a curved nail. That's not be right right behind the picture. That's not be there
That is be the why would I like you don't think that's either?
Okay, so we'll break this person
That's Katina Jimmy from uh, from Hocus Pocus. What are you talking about?
Who is it?
From Hocus Pocus, right?
Yeah, Katina, Katina, Katina Jimmy.
That's not me, that's not me.
So what would you rate this person?
She looks a lovely person.
That's not Vita. You don't think that's Vita?
I would Spunky, but I can't I just it's awarded a random the memberships
So
You don't think that's Vita, bro, you don't think that's Vita that's Vita 110% that's her nails too. She grow her nails out
Well, I know I was that they YouTube do need to change that they should allow you to pick who you who you want to give your membership to
That random shit is for the birds, you know
Yeah
Well, I mean it is a good way to support the show and you know, I will give you more cards every time I do a reading
You'd like a reading elbow. I got a reading for you today and
Anybody else want to come on panel or in the chat, but they can read you know, you know bust it up
You know, it's case though spur again did baiting it did Barry ever
You know talk to Kate again. I mean like what's going on, huh?
Said I'm even hearing that he paid Barry to get off fucking beat a panel so who knows what the fuck going on
Very gifted Schmelian membership. Yep
But it is at random though, yeah
Well, you know a Kate and be that I'm really a really happy that they're doing like long lives and like you know
They're interesting people. They you know, they got interesting content compelling content. Sometimes I'm a part of that
Sometimes I'm not but you know, I wish everyone the best in their channel. It's not a competition
I think there's eight. There's two billion people on YouTube. We can bring in a million people to this channel, you know, it's like
Or to all of our channels, right? We can we can you have huge channels. I think we're at the under
represented panel verse which is like you know how many people just know about oh there's these panels you can go on and you
can be a kind of be on TV and
and meet people and these tales and have these interesting conversations
buried down the chat, seeing the witness protection.
Yep, case nine. Oh, come on. All right, who are you calling?
My uncle. Okay.
Hello
Brandy who's Brandy?
We're calling Brandy
Come on, baby. I need to stop giving me these fake-ass fucking numbers, man
Brandy man, who the fuck
It's not a stripper's name. I was a stripper's name
Who y'all got me calling brother? I just called pebs best friend, bro. Cuz it sound like her
Oh my gosh, yeah, that's what's you look bad. Yeah, I don't think that's brandy brandy fuck
No, because this is a nah, I can't be so it's over. It's awesome. I can't man y'all
Yeah
For smelly, yeah
Yeah, that might be someone else in the band. I'm not sure. I'm not sure who that was guys that I mean
There's no brandy in the fan man, it's already been looked into I got all the names
Brandy nah, we might ask Kate
Somebody go and Kate go ask Kate. She knows brandy man. Damn it
You even know brandy
Okay, I'm gonna do this hold on. I gotta do this
This stupid ass
I got it I need some coffee. I don't know forget it
I haven't
Hot but whole lava that makes you. Oh
Who's the question
Okay, do you got a relative named Brandy
Huh, why you hang up bitch?
It's live right now
Well, she just answered
Elder are you remember you're saying what you didn't make a donation so you can call these people mentioned that now you're just calling them for free
Come on, man. You go on. Come on. I got you. Don't worry about it, man
Okay
God there you money hungry, man. You rich you get money you wealthy man. You a trust fund, baby
Are you doing me like that? I got
For somebody check to see if she spurred good man. I might it might have not been her. Let me see
No Kate no
Hello
He's muted up, okay, he's listening to what she's saying
Okay, that was her
That was you man. What'd you say? She blocked a fucking free number. I can always get another free number
Well, okay, that was not me that hit just for the record. He I'm he just did that
I know controller what he was doing. I'm not gonna hers that I
Okay, Jerry the hey, what's up Jerry haven't seen Jerry in a while. Good to see Jerry
Thank you
Ah
She got my number saved so I don't know why she answered she got it saved like so she knew it was me calling her
That was her sister-in-law she said
Hey, JT. What's up on the panel? You want to hang out? God, even, no, yeah. Or, I want to draw you.
Oh, that's her sister-in-law. What an idiot. Why would she tell people that I got the right number? Oh, my God.
Eldo, I'm going to draw you, okay, Eldo?
Oh, go ahead, go ahead. I'm smiling. Go ahead, go ahead.
Let me just look at you. Okay, smile like that.
You should.
Oh my God.
So that's her sister-in-law. Oh, I get it.
So that's her sister-in-law, which means she's married.
Okay, I got you. Okay, got it.
I get it now. So I still kind of got it right.
So you're really looking at my picture come on
Yeah, I got it
Want to see yeah, it's a come on you ain't
Really I guess that's good
Okay, I didn't I didn't know that he would do that. Hey, I didn't have control of it
He just was he was like I know he was calling me
Eldo tell me tell her I didn't have anything to do with it. No, you didn't have no he didn't even know I was gonna call shut the fuck up, bitch
He didn't even she didn't even know I was calling I'm calling random numbers such old stupid ass up hoe the fuck
Like Daniel
That's good
Yeah
Yeah, and it's like platform. I don't know
Everyone's saying someone's assuming me something. I don't I don't I don't have time to keep up with it. Yeah
One time I one time I called
I called Kate and she was like Papa John's and I was like hi can I order a bar of pizza and then she was like
Yeah
Was
Don't know. I don't know. It's a you know, and it's like people like
Doxers that will be like, oh my god
Bitch wasn't you wasn't that bitch just doxing fucking beta wasn't you just doxing her number on your fucking platform?
Why are you crying hoe?
And then you confirming numbers like that's the like you just confirmed a number like
God damn she gotta be a dumb bitch
Why would you confirm a number like?
Hey
She gotta be stupid man
Yeah, go get a new teddy bear bitch stop crying
She look at psych as weak she tried to take control of psych I don't like that
You know I'm saying don't be trying to take control of sight man. I think he weak. I think he's stupid
No, let's see
Yeah, I don't know guys, let me see. I'm kind of like it just I don't know. I'm interested in a coffee
I know
Okay, so she's gonna run my champs the ground now what she's been saying that's for months, please
Yeah, it gets ridiculous when people that do stuff and they're like when they step in it and then they're like oh my gosh
Then it's like what people do to them say if people do it to people that don't deserve it and that are not doing anything
That's one thing people are doing it back to people that are playing the same dirty game. Say what it's like
I was it dirty to call somebody. I just all I did was call a number that was given. I was just seeing who it was
They didn't even answer
I mean and then I called Kate Kate and me been talking so for those like how y'all think I got Kate number
She gave me her number. I'm not I didn't dox her number like she's doxing fucking beta
The fuck out of here. I'm not trying to hear that dumb shit. Let's am I a chest say some slick ass shit
I'm not trying to hit that shit
That bitch over there doxing fucking be the dad like the fuck I
Called the number didn't doxing nothing I called a number
I think I got the right to call.
I mean, the elbow is like, he's not like, try to start fuses.
Like, why do you do that on my piano?
No, but I didn't.
My no, but it's enough. But now she's mad at me and I say I didn't do anything
It's like something you did and it's like and then you know, it's like you're just like
Fucking a benefit
You know, I'm better. I do benefit what you mean. I'm a donator
Okay
She don't benefit you but all she do is threaten you man. Well, yeah, well next next when I'm doxxed and like you know
And then you already
They know where you live at you get you was getting pizzas at one point
Sight like all I did all I did was call a number. I didn't know if it was a correct number
I knew her number though, but who cares she gave me her number. I
Don't need docks more
She's not gonna do shit. She's already mad. She's she got a beat of the worry about
She got real charges coming her way. So trust me. You'll be alright. She'll be locked up by the time she can get to you
Either in a man in either in a mental asylum or a fucking prison a jail. I'll say jail. I
Think they won't give her no more than like five years
Got any order repeats. Hey delusional. How are you gonna say you're gonna take site channel down for a call?
What you gonna hit YouTube up and say or somebody called somebody on fucking sites channel?
It's gonna guys it's gonna a little bit ridiculous
Everybody's gonna take place on it for action. I don't know. It's like, you know
Guys if you you know if you wrestle with pigs no, no, I'm gonna say this now
I'm gonna say this now that I know no, I'm not even gonna say this
I suggest she I say if you still listen, I suggest you stop when you say here fucker with people that ain't fucking with you
You go you're gonna feel some you go you go your family gonna be looking at you sideways bitch
I'm just letting you know now
You gonna be getting phone calls just like be to get the phone call from her dad
You gonna be getting a phone call from your sister
Oh
Time to a beat oh get a fucking free beat
Drinks dessert beers coffee coffee coffee
Yeah, like, you know, no juice hard. She don't need a real hobby. She needs to get back in
Find a job and stop collecting it the fucking unemployment only lasts so long
Unemployment she really is she really telling the truth and she's really living on her own like I don't how
Like nah, man
Like is she getting ebt now
Is the bitch getting Section 8?
Uh?
Is she about to be a peps?
I'm just saying, man.
She might, she might be gonna...
Oh, shit.
How's everyone doing? W. L. Dole. Hold me. See you. They have any coffee. Yeah, I'll drink coffee
I'm just looking at the dishwasher, okay dishwasher, okay
Okay, wow, they do advanced packs. Okay, just washing okay got it starting your
Dishwashing okay got that got the
Wish I get you were reading yes master you can
Master once a reading okay, I'm a master. I'll do from the villains for you. I have a feeling the villains deck what you're
Yes, you can foster man foster man I got the car, okay
Also, we have wheel of fortune
There's a spinning wheel wheel of fortune, you know always got someone lurking behind it
But it looks like it's going in the upright for you. Looks like things are
Going well good luck coming to you you're able to
Manifest right now. I'll say the wheel of force number 10 actually on the back. It says wheel of fortune
Since this is Maleficent's cursed spinning wheel changes the course of Aurora's life,
the Wheel of Fortune represents pivotal moments that change in luck and twist and fate.
The Wheel of Fortune is a reminder that life is unpredictable, your luck is ever changing.
When this tarot card is drawn is a clear sign to expect the unexpected.
Appreciate where you are in life right now because big changes are on the way
Whether you're offered an amazing new opportunity
Or you prick your finger on a cursed spinning wheel the wheel of fortune reminds you that your life can change in an instant
Live in the moment, right? Isn't that true?
What else we got for you, ooh
Six of swords, okay
It's a six of swords card six of swords, you know
Maybe not everything's been going perfectly or you're kind of guarded right now
It says the six of course indicates you're recently been through a difficult time
Unexpected setbacks can be demoralizing but don't let them drain you completely the situation is salvageable and don't despair
Maybe there's been something on with your luck or your fortune. You're worried about it right now
Finally, oh got the Empress card. Oh, this is oh, but this is like this is mother Gothel
And some other golf was the Empress, okay, there's a woman in your future or some kind of
A fertility abundance is like Mother Gothel, the Empress is a powerful and maternal figure
who places a high value on beauty.
Mother Gothel uses the magic flower to keep her youthful appearance for hundreds of years.
But when the flower's magic is transferred to Rapunzel, Gothel is determined to stay
young by any means necessary, even if it means keeping Rapunzel locked away in a tower.
The Empress reminds you to appreciate the beauty all around you, but remember...
Beauty is more than skin deep.
Now is the time to nurture your friendships
and connect with the magic and splendor of nature.
Gather some friends for a stroll outside.
Enjoy the fresh air, enchanted flowers,
princesses and towers.
Who knows the magic you'll stumble upon.
I don't know because, well, Eldor did a print call.
Also 10 of cups, so this is really good.
This is a 10 of cups, this is a great.
Omen for the future, you know, Ten of Cups is like the family happiness happy family times
Everything's growing good. Ten of Cups represents happiness within your home family and close friend circle
You're feeling supported understood appreciated. Lucky you let your loved ones know how much you love and appreciate them
Okay, hope you like that
You like prank call, oh, yeah, I didn't know I didn't know what he was doing. I didn't know he was doing that
You're in love with me Yogg-tard. Thank you. I'm in love with you too. Hi guys
Why are you still talking about it? I thought we moved on from this shit. What the fuck who bringing it up?
And when the chat someone said
Are you talking to me or somebody else?
Me you're gonna be
I'm asking like who brought it up like why who's talking about it?
Oh, someone said fucking looking fucking fucking fucking look fucking low key said why is everyone talking about kid?
I thought this was a tarot channel and so I just mentioned don't worry about it low key. Why are you dick riding?
Okay, go suck up go suck on her titty bitch
Fuck around with you, bro
Okay
So
How's everyone doing let me see
Can I turn you straight master man build comm ones to turn me straight low key says don't talk to them. Okay
Hennessey's terrible Mexican cantina I
Have it. Oh, they're a copy. Is it a copy shake. I'm going for the coffee shake. Please be a coffee shake
The coffee shake a coffee shake, please hop up. They have a cop guys. They have a top. They have a coffee shake. Okay
Yes
Getting it getting it coffee shake. Well, so good
They have the
Barbecue, oh, I want the
Charburger meal
That I get the regular drink as a coffee
I can't get a
Fuck off like that. I'll say the burger. Okay
Yeah, I'll be put you double char with cheese on the double char with cheese char burger with cheese barbecue bacon
Teriyaki, okay, that's all teriyaki
So total
Okay, perfect. Okay, I got it. I'm getting more food
Okay, let's do it. Let's do it. Fuck it
What do you think although should I just go do it? I did it already
Can do case yeah
You saw is that true, I mean is that that fake is that a fake Barry's butt I
Didn't know Barry was so hairy
But let's not make any jokes about dingleberries that would just be gross
Guys we get shake it high and shake it high
Yeah, here we go. I'll get high on the baby
Elder can you pray call clausterman build calm
You said what site can you
Have you
Can I what I
Missed it. Just hit elder prank call me cluster man. Oh, no, okay. I can't do it because
Kate is
Threatening psychs fucking discord. So why would I you know saying I can't do it. I can't do it. No, you cannot pray call
No, I can't can't talk about Kate right now. We talk about I'm listening to what's like saying right now
He's reading third reading sir. What's going on? What's going on? Are you guys feeling about me right now?
No, nope. Nope. She moved on so
She's actually reviewing your she's she's reviewing. She's she's reviewing your channel, but she wants to take down your channel
So make it make sense
Okay, she's reviewing your live with be the same man
a raging and a couple other people in you.
But she wants to take you down.
If she takes you down,
she ain't gonna have content like that.
Well, please, bigger people
who tried to take me down than her.
Okay, you like that life?
Yeah.
You never seen a white woman that resembles you.
Yeah, apparently it was good.
I'm gonna have to watch it.
Is it under memberships?
Which video?
The one would be done. Um, did you put it on your memberships?
No, it's just it's it's just still this uh, this this uh, this live right here. We're talking about right now
Oh, is this lie?
Yeah, I was gonna play to put it on their memberships, but you still live. Okay. Okay. Okay. It was this one
I'm going to put it on your membership. So guys if you want to watch this live you got a
Membership. I'll see you soon. I'll be I'll be right back